1241490299215634434	official death toll from #covid19 in the united kingdom is now greater than: germany + poland + switzerland + austria + portugal + greece + sweden + finland + norway + ireland... combined. uk: 67.5 million (233 dead) above group: 185 million (230 dead) httpurl	INFORMATIVE	GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL	the_united_kingdom/GPE germany/GPE poland/GPE switzerland/GPE austria/GPE portugal/GPE greece/GPE sweden/GPE finland/GPE norway_+/GPE ireland/GPE uk/GPE 67.5_million/CARDINAL 233/CARDINAL 185_million/CARDINAL 230/CARDINAL
1245916400981381130	dearest mr. president @user 1,169 coronavirus deaths in the us in 24 hours (?) covid19 pandemic is an international crime from china - not a nature disasster! please use your authorities to protect your people and world against china! #chinahastocompensateall	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL GPE TIME GPE GPE	1,169/CARDINAL us/GPE 24_hours/TIME china/GPE china/GPE
1241132432402849793	"latest updates march 20 ⚠️5274 new cases and 38 new deaths in the united states illinois: governo pritzker issues ""stay at home"" order for all residents new york: governor cuomo orders 100% of all non-essential workers to stay home penns...source ( /coronavirus/country/us/ )"	INFORMATIVE	DATE CARDINAL GPE GPE PERSON GPE PERSON PERCENT PERSON	march_20/DATE 38/CARDINAL the_united_states/GPE illinois/GPE governo_pritzker/PERSON new_york/GPE cuomo/PERSON 100%/PERCENT penns/PERSON
1236107253666607104	真把公主不当干部 breaking: 21 people on grand princess cruise ship docked off the california coast tested positive for coronavirus, including 19 crew members and two passengers, vice pres. mike pence says. 24 people tested negative. httpurl httpurl	INFORMATIVE	PERSON CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL PERSON CARDINAL	真把公主不当干部/PERSON 21/CARDINAL california/GPE 19/CARDINAL two/CARDINAL mike_pence/PERSON 24/CARDINAL
1239673817552879619	oklahoma city — the state department of education announced monday the closure of all k-12 public schools statewide until at least april 6 as the number of covid-19 cases climb and the risk of community spread grows. httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE ORG DATE DATE CARDINAL	oklahoma_city/GPE the_state_department_of_education/ORG monday/DATE at_least_april_6/DATE covid-19/CARDINAL
1240790181860409344	"democrats somehow managed to fight ebola without calling it ""the african virus."" a cluster of covid-19 cases has emerged in new york city's hassidic neighborhood, so it's only a matter of time before the local trump klux klan starts talking about ""the jew virus."""	UNINFORMATIVE	NORP NORP GPE GPE ORG NORP	democrats/NORP african/NORP covid-19/GPE new_york_city's/GPE trump_klux_klan/ORG jew/NORP
1249147011003187200	as number of #covid19 deaths surpassed 100,000 worldwide, ny surpassed italy on number of recorded deaths 🔥😷🇺🇸 new york state has more coronavirus cases than any country worldwide httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG CARDINAL GPE GPE QUANTITY GPE	covid19/ORG 100,000/CARDINAL ny/GPE italy/GPE 😷🇺🇸/QUANTITY new_york/GPE
1241533144802758656	@user @user 1 week ago today (march 14), there were only 115 cases of covid in fl. today, last count was at 763... that is a 563% increase in 1 week due to your “slave to trump” incompetence. imagine next saturday if there is another 563% increase-we will be at 9300+. resign	INFORMATIVE	DATE DATE DATE CARDINAL NORP GPE DATE CARDINAL PERCENT DATE DATE PERCENT	1_week_ago/DATE today/DATE march_14/DATE only_115/CARDINAL covid/NORP fl/GPE today/DATE 763/CARDINAL 563%/PERCENT 1_week/DATE next_saturday/DATE 563%/PERCENT
1236363091002011649	"“coronavirus impact: close taj mahal till march end, agra mayor urges” “people scared of foreigners and looked at them with suspicion, situation could turn nasty and tarnish india's image internationally,"" he said. not possible to tarnish india further. httpurl"	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON DATE GPE GPE GPE	taj_mahal/PERSON march_end/DATE agra/GPE india/GPE india/GPE
1245725162957242368	"dear @user in #covid2019 case...give tools &amp; machines to #bangladesh, ""not money"". bcoz, #climate fund money was stolen by the ruling party. @user @user @user @user @user @user @user @user @user httpurl"	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE ORG ORG ORG	#bangladesh/GPE bcoz/ORG #climate_fund/ORG the_ruling_party/ORG
1240721152076546049	los angeles is now the county with the highest number of coronavirus cases in california. @user breaks down the impact of #covid19 on la, from cancelled college commencements to haphazard health screenings at lax airport. #cheddarlive httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE GPE	los_angeles/GPE california/GPE
1246739551227387905	#covid19 updates. #sothsudan's fist positive patient is a 29 yo dutch, who arrived in the country from netherlands via addis ababa on 28 february. #ssot httpurl	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL NORP GPE GPE DATE PERSON	29/CARDINAL dutch/NORP netherlands/GPE addis_ababa/GPE 28_february/DATE #ssot/PERSON
1242799513619664896	watch live !! discussion on #covid19 with union health minister dr harsh vardhan, union health secretary ms preeti sudan &amp; dg icmr, dr balram bhargava httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON PERSON ORG PERSON PERSON	dr_harsh_vardhan/PERSON ms_preeti/PERSON sudan_&amp/ORG dg_icmr/PERSON balram_bhargava/PERSON
1251122786225045504	coronavirus cases in africa could shoot up from thousands now to 10 million within three to six months according to very provisional modelling, a regional @user official said on thursday. @user httpurl httpurl httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	LOC CARDINAL CARDINAL DATE ORG DATE	africa/LOC thousands/CARDINAL 10_million/CARDINAL three_to_six_months/DATE @user/ORG thursday/DATE
1241449715654410240	“according to their report if you come in contact with someone who tests positive for covid-19 you have a 1–5% chance of catching it as well.” who’s report? the world health organization. this is a long read but very worth while httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	DATE PERCENT ORG	covid-19/DATE 1–5%/PERCENT the_world_health_organization/ORG
1241173819693252608	senators urge jeff bezos to give amazon warehouse workers sick leave, hazard pay - cnbc: * senators urge jeff bezos to give amazon warehouse workers sick leave, hazard pay cnbc * amazon warehouse workers fear catching coronavirus just to get you your… httpurl httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON ORG ORG PERSON ORG ORG ORG	jeff_bezos/PERSON amazon_warehouse/ORG cnbc/ORG jeff_bezos/PERSON amazon_warehouse/ORG cnbc/ORG amazon_warehouse/ORG
1245311331579899906	a @user professor has died after contracting #coronavirus a book of condolence will be available online soon for professor peter sinclair from the department of economics. httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG CARDINAL PERSON ORG	@user/ORG #/CARDINAL peter_sinclair/PERSON the_department_of_economics/ORG
1240108182409601024	eu imposes entry ban for 30 days while death toll in the united states mounts to 100; death toll in italy due to #coronavirus crosses 2100; spain, colombia, malaysia and canada seal borders #covid19 #coronaviruspandemic #cuarentenanacional #cuarentenacoronavirus #coronaalert httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG DATE GPE CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL GPE GPE GPE GPE MONEY	eu/ORG 30_days/DATE the_united_states/GPE 100/CARDINAL italy/GPE #/CARDINAL 2100/CARDINAL spain/GPE colombia/GPE malaysia/GPE canada/GPE #covid19_#/MONEY
1248321628808728576	إِنَّا لِلّهِ وَإِنَّـا إِلَيْهِ رَاجِعُونَ sad to hear about passing away of syed mehdi shah brother in law of cm sindh @user he was tested positive with #covid_19 may allah rest his soul in peace.	INFORMATIVE	PERSON ORG	syed_mehdi_shah_brother/PERSON allah/ORG
1236128165745094663	@user carma &amp; her family in san jose, ca, are possibly infected with #coronavirus since 6 feb in seattle. way way more than 1,000 cases in seattle now... httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG GPE DATE GPE CARDINAL GPE	carma_&amp/ORG san_jose/GPE 6_feb/DATE seattle/GPE more_than_1,000/CARDINAL seattle/GPE
1244684987351404551	i think the president cyril ramaphosa should address us every day, monday - friday at 18:30 throughout this ordeal 🤷‍♂️ #covid_19 #coronavirusinsa #lockdownsa	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON DATE TIME PRODUCT MONEY	cyril_ramaphosa/PERSON monday_-_friday/DATE 18:30/TIME 🤷/PRODUCT #covid_19_#coronavirusinsa_#lockdownsa/MONEY
1242951300184076288	day 8 shout out goes to kevin ⁦@user for his great coverage of covid 19 and community responses and needs coupled with applause to ⁦@user med students who are tracking positive peeps contacts!!! httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON ORG ORG	kevin_⁦@user/PERSON covid_19/ORG ⁦@user_med/ORG
1241183452243693568	@user we don’t want to argue. we want you racists in the @user to freaking stop calling it the “chinese virus.” that is disgusting. it is stirring up bigotry and hatred. we are not arguing. and people are dying. you are hateful #racist scum. stfu. #covid2019 #coronacrisis	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG NORP	@user/ORG chinese/NORP
1241076120742768640	half of uruguay’s covid-19 cases can be traced to a single fashion designer httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	CARDINAL GPE DATE	half/CARDINAL uruguay/GPE covid-19/DATE
1244676665990696961	e don happen!!! casala don burst!!! governor of oyo state, seyi makinde, has tested positive to the deadly coronavirus, few days after holding a political rally in the state. #coronavirustruth	INFORMATIVE	PERSON ORG PERSON DATE	casala_don/PERSON oyo_state/ORG seyi_makinde/PERSON few_days/DATE
1248774057018806272	the line of cars just seems to get longer. these folks demand @user release migrants held here in eloy to try and stop spread of covid. human rights groups say at least two migrants in the detention center tested positive for virus. @user httpurl	INFORMATIVE	GPE NORP CARDINAL	eloy/GPE covid/NORP at_least_two/CARDINAL
1244181629784002561	trump was wrong! he bed his election on shutting down virus!cdc issues domestic travel advisory as coronavirus deaths double to over 2,000 within two days httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG CARDINAL DATE	trump/ORG over_2,000/CARDINAL two_days/DATE
1246972644416786440	most #workplaces to close for one month from apr 7 to curb spread of #covid-19” &amp; all the #singapore morning #news you need to know on one page for april 6, 2020 via @user #sarscovs #coronavirus #covip19 #independentjournalism in #cambodia httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	CARDINAL DATE DATE CARDINAL DATE MONEY MONEY GPE	#/CARDINAL one_month/DATE apr_7/DATE one/CARDINAL april_6,_2020/DATE #sarscovs_#/MONEY #covip19_#/MONEY #cambodia/GPE
1241782755412914177	kentucky republican rand paul is the first us senator to tested positive for covid-19. house members diaz-balart (r-fl) and mcadams (d-ut) tested positive for coronavirus earlier this month.	INFORMATIVE	GPE NORP PERSON ORDINAL GPE DATE ORG PERSON ORG PERSON DATE	kentucky/GPE republican/NORP rand_paul/PERSON first/ORDINAL us/GPE covid-19/DATE house/ORG diaz-balart/PERSON r-fl/ORG mcadams/PERSON earlier_this_month/DATE
1245114106497163270	"writing in fp, @user &amp; @user have penned their case against lifting iran sanx over the #covid pandemic. mark and rich are two of the smartest &amp; most influential advocates of the ""max pressure"" policy, and well worth reading. a few thoughts: httpurl"	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG ORG GPE PERSON CARDINAL	@user_&amp/ORG @user/ORG iran/GPE mark/PERSON two/CARDINAL
1236091525102268419	i have a place in philly and most of my family live in the general area. i’m traveling, a friend sent me this: “one floor of doylestown hospital is quarantined, central bucks school district shut down. coronavirus has arrived wth.”	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE CARDINAL ORG ORG	philly/GPE one/CARDINAL doylestown_hospital/ORG central_bucks/ORG
1236148083504775168	on friday, aipac announced that two attendees had tested positive for covid-19 coronavirus. mike pence and mitch mcconnell were both in attendance. others are being self quarantined but not attendees from the us. why? httpurl	INFORMATIVE	DATE ORG CARDINAL DATE PERSON PERSON GPE	friday/DATE aipac/ORG two/CARDINAL covid-19/DATE mike_pence/PERSON mitch_mcconnell/PERSON us/GPE
1235899315207450625	as #coronavirus spreads, democratic republic of congo discharges last #ebola patient httpurl via @user	UNINFORMATIVE	CARDINAL GPE	#/CARDINAL democratic_republic_of_congo/GPE
1245292834057576448	the city of #stl will start tracking positive cases of #covid19 by zip code. @user has your info this morning, live, from city hall. #tisl @user httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	TIME	this_morning/TIME
1245880624482664449	thread: join @user speaks to human rights lawyer @user and infectious diseases doctor daisy tagarda • gov't eyes mass testing for suspected covid-19 cases on april 14 • nbi probes netizens spreading fake news • dr. tagarda shares story from the frontlines httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG ORG PERSON GPE DATE ORG PERSON PERSON	@user/ORG @user/ORG daisy_tagarda_•_gov't/PERSON covid-19/GPE april_14/DATE nbi/ORG •_dr/PERSON tagarda/PERSON
1241182759449739265	check your email and visit the residence life covid19 plan for details on staying and checking out: httpurl httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE		
1245863053662367747	the lss choices crisis hotline is available to help anyone experiencing #domesticviolence in franklin county. call 614-224-4663 24/7 love shouldn't hurt. #lssnetworkofhope experts fear domestic violence cases could rise during coronavirus outbreak httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG GPE CARDINAL PERSON	lss/ORG franklin_county/GPE 614/CARDINAL #lssnetworkofhope/PERSON
1238874923965136896	#surgeongeneral just said 98% to 99% will recover. #coronavirusupdates #coronavirus httpurl if 99% will recover why is the world economy shutting down? why did the media lie that this virus has a 3.5% mortality rate? it's a #nwo control plan.	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG PERCENT MONEY PERCENT PERCENT ORG	#surgeongeneral/ORG 98%_to_99%/PERCENT #coronavirusupdates_#/MONEY 99%/PERCENT 3.5%/PERCENT nwo/ORG
1249803325199040515	inside louisiana's horrifying 'cancer alley,' an 85-mile stretch of pollution and environmental racism that's now dealing with some of the highest coronavirus death rates in the country httpurl james pasley apr 9, 2020, 7:42 pm (continued 4) httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE PERSON DATE TIME CARDINAL	louisiana/GPE james_pasley/PERSON apr_9,_2020/DATE 7:42_pm/TIME 4/CARDINAL
1242812989130055680	"@user issues ""stay at home"" order issued for vt! httpurl effective 5:00pm today until april 15th. please read the order for businesses that are deemed ""essential"". #vermontstrong #covid19 #thankyourgrocers #thankyournurses #thankyourdoctors #stayhome"	UNINFORMATIVE	DATE DATE PERSON MONEY	today/DATE april_15th/DATE #vermontstrong_#covid19_#thankyourgrocers_#thankyournurses/PERSON #thankyourdoctors_#/MONEY
1245771047435218945	@user @user @user @user @user @user they both are relief hospitals provided by the federal government and federal protocols govern who can be admitted. guess the feds are not that keen to ensure non-coronavirus cases get admitted to their hospitals so @user can put corona patients in our regular hospitals	UNINFORMATIVE		
1244578159976054785	3. st. xavier’s school, shivajinagar 4. st. lourdes school, cubbonpet 5. st. lourdes school, halasuru (ulsoor) please share #covid2019	UNINFORMATIVE	CARDINAL PERSON ORG ORG ORG ORG ORG	3/CARDINAL st._xavier/PERSON shivajinagar_4/ORG st._lourdes_school/ORG cubbonpet_5/ORG st._lourdes_school/ORG halasuru/ORG
1236152372088442880	usat: aipac says 2 pple at dc conf. attended by pence &amp; others, tested positive for coronavirus the american israel public affairs committee told conf. attendees, some of whom include lawmakers, that at least 2 conf-goers have tested positive for covid-19 httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG ORG CARDINAL ORG NORP GPE CARDINAL	usat/ORG aipac/ORG 2/CARDINAL pence_&amp/ORG american/NORP israel/GPE at_least_2/CARDINAL
1245730086457876487	motorhomes / rv's for overworked healthcare workers? a thought occurred to me in reading about how #healthcare workers are a) so overworked and tired after their shifts, and b) so anxious over bringing #covid19 back to their families, c) in some cases s…httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG ORG	motorhomes_/_rv's/ORG #healthcare_workers/ORG
1236128441956630534	#australia melbourne gp clinic closed after doctor tests positive for #coronavirus after seeing 70 patients this month - abc news httpurl via @user	INFORMATIVE	ORG CARDINAL CARDINAL DATE ORG	#australia_melbourne_gp_clinic/ORG #/CARDINAL 70/CARDINAL this_month/DATE abc_news/ORG
1245717847415930880	🚨senator loeffler and her husband “sold shares in retail stores such as lululemon and t.j. maxx and invested in a company that makes covid-19 protective garments.” in case governors were still wondering why price gouging on ppe products hasn’t halted.🤨 httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON ORG ORG GPE	loeffler/PERSON lululemon/ORG t.j._maxx/ORG covid-19/GPE
1241410720555765762	georgia in the coronavirus age: chaos, bad news, mounting deaths more than 300 patients from cruise ship with + covid land in atlanta. during flight, 3 found to test positive, 1 sick. cdc screened remaining patients &amp; released them to fly home. crazy httpurl	INFORMATIVE	GPE CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL ORG ORG	georgia/GPE more_than_300/CARDINAL atlanta/GPE 3/CARDINAL 1/CARDINAL cdc/ORG &amp/ORG
1245640235871956993	according to cmo lucknow dr narendra agarwal: samples were taken of 25 people who had attended the tabglighi jamaat event. all 25 people have been tested negative for covid19. @user @user	INFORMATIVE	ORG PERSON CARDINAL NORP CARDINAL	cmo_lucknow_dr/ORG narendra_agarwal/PERSON 25/CARDINAL jamaat/NORP 25/CARDINAL
1246018084478939136	(update) the indian #rupee fell against the us #dollar recently. indian #coronavirus cases risk exponentially growing with manufacturing slowing. $usdinr may rise but it faces fading momentum #india #rbi - ... httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	NORP MONEY NORP ORG	indian/NORP #rupee/MONEY indian/NORP usdinr/ORG
1245863461646561282	#yemen if any covid19 case shows up in yemen, god forbid, then we hold the saudico regimes &amp; their masters full responsibility. game over gestapo, your biological warfare isn't going to break will of the people of yemen. cholera &amp; diptheria are examples httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE GPE ORG GPE ORG	#yemen/GPE yemen/GPE the_saudico_regimes_&amp/ORG yemen/GPE cholera_&amp/ORG
1244711847074213889	when you divide the coronavirus stimulus package by the population of america and remember that the virus was first announced 6666 days after the 9/11 attacks. 🧐 httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE DATE CARDINAL	america/GPE 6666_days/DATE 9/11/CARDINAL
1236113067039027200	mathematically, the overall death rate from #covid19 is 3.3% (3412 dead out of 100,775 cases. death rate china is 3.7% death rate s. korea is 4.6% 👉🏼but the death rate in iran is horrific. it is 25.9%⁉️ httpurl	INFORMATIVE	PERCENT CARDINAL CARDINAL GPE PERCENT GPE PERCENT GPE CARDINAL	3.3%/PERCENT 3412/CARDINAL 100,775/CARDINAL china/GPE 3.7%/PERCENT s._korea/GPE 4.6%/PERCENT iran/GPE 25.9%⁉️/CARDINAL
1242841682648936449	a california highway patrol officer stationed in oakland has tested positive for the coronavirus, the latest bay area law enforcement officer to be diagnosed with the virus, authorities said. httpurl	INFORMATIVE	GPE GPE LOC	california/GPE oakland/GPE bay_area/LOC
1243534385598496768	sad! 2 #coronavirusindia suicides! man commits suicide over coronavirus suspicion in dakshina karnataka. another middle-aged man from uppoor village in neighbouring udupi district ended his life on wednesday after suspecting that he had the covid-19 infection -- pti	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL GPE GPE GPE DATE DATE	2_#/CARDINAL dakshina_karnataka/GPE uppoor_village/GPE udupi/GPE wednesday/DATE covid-19/DATE
1237344256458657792	it will get worse since @user and the politically correct gang who are pawns of the un's @user will promote the spread of the virus through international travel into canada ontario confirms three new covid-19 cases httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG ORG GPE CARDINAL	@user/ORG un/ORG canada_ontario/GPE three/CARDINAL
1241636547365134336	just read this ‘incredibly worrying. covid-19 cases confirmed in gaza’ and geno felt bad for paul he’s been through so much lol good eyes old man	INFORMATIVE	GPE PERSON PERSON	gaza/GPE geno/PERSON paul/PERSON
1236183073273688064	heard about the news regarding an employee in bgc, specifically netlima building (where i worked before) who’s tested positive for #covid19. to my bgc friends and hangout buddies, my ex-officemates and colleagues who are still working there, you guys take care and be vigilant. 😔	INFORMATIVE	ORG FAC ORG	bgc/ORG netlima_building/FAC bgc/ORG
1245659811108159495	come on &amp; he must stop another hateful useless episode especially at such a time of disaster with the corona virus. he must stop the hate &amp; shameful &amp; disgraceful actions. adam schiff must forget &amp; must stop the hating especially at such a time of disaster with the corona virus.	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG PERSON	&amp/ORG adam_schiff/PERSON
1250494185729335296	@user it's what they do.. remember the imaginary extra 20,000 police.. the 20 hospitals that were 8 then 2. imaginary help for sme's, self-employed.. imaginary #covid19 testing.. imaginary #ppe.. imaginary ventilators.. invisible care home deaths.. httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL	20,000/CARDINAL 20/CARDINAL 8/CARDINAL 2/CARDINAL
1241313082376425472	the corona virus cases in ghana is moving like the eve people's dance.... it moves forward, comes back and move forward again ... 19 #covid_19 cases now ehii 🙊🙊💔	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE CARDINAL ORG	ghana/GPE 19/CARDINAL ehii_🙊🙊/ORG
1241179161588387840	an update on our efforts to secure covid-19 test kits for the city of mobile: httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	DATE	covid-19/DATE
1251869634279718915	@user mr president ask evers in wisconsin to open our economy. he has us on lockdown until may 26. we have 170 deaths attributed to covid-19. i think 170 is an inflated number. last year our entire deaths were 140. we are not a hotbed. we need to open	INFORMATIVE	PERSON GPE DATE CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL DATE CARDINAL	evers/PERSON wisconsin/GPE may_26/DATE 170/CARDINAL covid-19/GPE 170/CARDINAL last_year/DATE 140/CARDINAL
1245672947873918976	health-care workers make up 9.6% of confirmed covid-19 cases in ontario, @user has learned from government data. that includes doctors, nurses, paramedics, personal support workers, long-term care home staff and other health-care professionals: httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	PERCENT DATE GPE ORG	9.6%/PERCENT covid-19/DATE ontario/GPE @user/ORG
1244533791399575552	delighted to hear that friend @user has been discharged from hospital after having covid-19. i heard of her husband @user she's at home &amp; was having a brew. what a fighter you are linda. wishing the family good health, love @user x #localradio #darloradio httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG ORG PERSON	@user/ORG home_&amp/ORG linda/PERSON
1241173784272363525	we're just like everybody else - hunkered down at the moment. @user talked to local olympians with concerns about training for #tokyo2020 amid coronavirus shutdowns. httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	NORP	olympians/NORP
1246037020641640449	"@user @user trump is no friend to veterans. trump was advised about covid-19 on aircraft carrier theodore roosevelt...did nothing! trump said soldiers suffering tbi had ""headaches"" after bombed! soldier's wanting the 1.3% raise ""unpatriotic"" ""like soldier's who weren't pow's"" deported 800 httpurl"	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON PERSON PERSON PERSON ORG PERCENT	trump/PERSON trump/PERSON theodore_roosevelt/PERSON trump/PERSON tbi/ORG 1.3%/PERCENT
1241164368588328961	washington state has 148 new #covid19 cases totaling 1,524 (source: @user ... growth appears linear looking back, unclear about the next five days ... looking decent @user #seattlecoronavirus httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG CARDINAL CARDINAL DATE	washington_state/ORG 148/CARDINAL 1,524/CARDINAL the_next_five_days/DATE
1245890265447043074	mike dudley was known as ‘pastor’ to many in baltimore. the 61-year-old died just days after being diagnosed with covid-19. i talked with his family about the legacy he leaves behind, as well as a heart wrenching reality of this virus — dying in the hosptial w/out family. httpurl	INFORMATIVE	PERSON GPE DATE DATE GPE	mike_dudley/PERSON baltimore/GPE 61-year-old/DATE just_days/DATE covid-19/GPE
1241135058569900036	"“this evening we were notified that a member of the office of the vice president tested positive for the coronavirus,"" pence's press secretary, katie miller, said in a statement."	INFORMATIVE	TIME PERSON	this_evening/TIME katie_miller/PERSON
1247111405276483585	#breaking: the ministry of health on monday announced another religious gathering cluster of #covid19 that took place in kuching, sarawak, in which two deaths and 83 positive cases have been recorded. httpurl httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG DATE GPE GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL	the_ministry_of_health/ORG monday/DATE kuching/GPE sarawak/GPE two/CARDINAL 83/CARDINAL
1241595312730497029	a governor issuing a presser on #covidー19 case in oyo state while #fmoh and @user are doing the same shows a gap in coordination. the unwarranted gap has left a dent on the # of cases in nigeria. cases now 23 in nigeria and not 22. the oyo case wasn't counted at 22	INFORMATIVE	ORG GPE CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL ORG CARDINAL	oyo_state/ORG nigeria/GPE 23/CARDINAL nigeria/GPE 22/CARDINAL oyo/ORG 22/CARDINAL
1245721411676758018	attn #srls: upcoming free webinar on april 7th! topic: covid-19 related information for srls: adjournments, legal paperwork, &amp; urgent cases. led by julie, and family lawyers aisha amjad &amp; georgette makhoul. more details on the facebook page here: httpurl #a2j httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON DATE ORG PERSON ORG PERSON ORG	attn_#srls/PERSON april_7th/DATE &amp/ORG julie/PERSON aisha_amjad_&amp/ORG georgette_makhoul/PERSON facebook/ORG
1236104801244438528	"trump is hoping that warmer weather will kill this ""superbug"" as was the case with #sars , has anyone noticed that the west coast appears to be the epicentre of #covid #covidー19 related deaths? just asking mr. prez.."	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG LOC MONEY PERSON	trump/ORG the_west_coast/LOC #covid_#covidー19/MONEY prez/PERSON
1245874722988085248	"@user @user ""lead"", sarah? sitting on the info for months, lying about it, and then creating the world's biggest clusterfu#k in trying to manage it. everyone see's, and hears, what trump* has done. he's a joke! #covid19 #covid19pandemic #trumpliespeopledie"	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON DATE PERSON MONEY	sarah/PERSON months/DATE trump/PERSON #covid19_#covid19pandemic_#trumpliespeopledie/MONEY
1243101268597280768	three more #coronavirus positive cases confirmed in #telangana today. among 3 positive cases, 2 of them are doctors from domalguda in #hyderabad &amp; 3rd one is a 49-year-old male resident of qutbullapur in medchal. with this number of #covid19 cases in ts has increased to 44 httpurl	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL CARDINAL DATE CARDINAL CARDINAL ORG ORDINAL DATE CARDINAL	three/CARDINAL #/CARDINAL today/DATE 3/CARDINAL 2/CARDINAL domalguda/ORG 3rd/ORDINAL 49-year-old/DATE 44/CARDINAL
1247736993238433792	covid-19: did jesus stop being that great doctor, the doctor of doctors? my dear, black / african « sheep », but where has your jesus christ, the doctor of doctors gone? in fact, more than 1,034 priests, bishops and nuns died from the corona virus httpurl	INFORMATIVE	DATE PERSON NORP ORG PERSON CARDINAL	covid-19/DATE jesus/PERSON black_/_african/NORP »/ORG jesus_christ/PERSON more_than_1,034/CARDINAL
1245869543517376512	@user hmm.. now why, oh why would #biden still be opposed to #medicareforall during a #pandemic that's so far seen 10m+ people lose both their job &amp; #healthinsurance.. &amp; said he'd even veto it, if it passed through his congress?🤔 #nojoe #nomiddleground #dnckillsvoters #covid19	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON PERSON CARDINAL PERSON ORG PERSON	#biden/PERSON #medicareforall/PERSON 10m+/CARDINAL #healthinsurance/PERSON congress/ORG 🤔_#nojoe/PERSON
1246422722428583936	who reversals during #covid19 (1) no human-to-human transmission (2) not yet an emergency (pheic) (3) no need for travel restrictions (4) no need for universal mask wearing this is what happens when the un and who puts politics infront of human lives	UNINFORMATIVE	CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL ORG	2/CARDINAL 3/CARDINAL 4/CARDINAL un/ORG
1244910753297006592	more recoveries! the department of health reports 7 new covid-19 recoveries, bringing the total number of recovered patients to 49. please stay at home! #covid19ph httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG CARDINAL CARDINAL	the_department_of_health/ORG 7/CARDINAL 49/CARDINAL
1236484280886403073	httpurl coronavirus: experiment gone wrong? two wuhan lab leaks exposed by chinese scientists i had my suspicion of the origin of the virus!😉👍	UNINFORMATIVE	CARDINAL GPE NORP PERSON	two/CARDINAL wuhan/GPE chinese/NORP 😉👍/PERSON
1241987899840696320	suspect food retail sales up a lot in jersey, supermarkets will need more people as the #covidー19 crisis develops. some comfort for hospitality &amp; non food retail staff losing jobs, there maybe another one.	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE ORG	jersey/GPE hospitality_&amp/ORG
1241241557245857797	this coronavirus case is really serious. even boko haram is working from home.🤣🤣🤣 httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON PERSON	boko_haram/PERSON 🤣🤣🤣/PERSON
1241083119832268801	montco pa coronavirus update- encouraging people to take advantage of 90 miles of trails in the county but continue to use social distancing.	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON QUANTITY	montco_pa/PERSON 90_miles/QUANTITY
1243163310356418568	hometown heroes! meet the new jersey restaurant owner who took out a $50,000 credit line so he could continue to pay employees during the covid-19 closing! httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE MONEY DATE	new_jersey/GPE 50,000/MONEY covid-19/DATE
1240801912955392000	cdc says n95 masks can be used for 8 hrs of continuous or intermittent use, should be discarded after interaction w/an infected patient. many dr’s around us said they are being given 1 to use indefinitely, they spray it down w/ lysol or wipe it off, unsure it will help. #covid19	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG ORG TIME CARDINAL	cdc/ORG n95/ORG 8_hrs/TIME 1/CARDINAL
1241591882465107968	@user plz convince all catholic churches, esp in ft lauderdale to stop allowing gatherings!we know a person who has been attending church because there is a belief that”god will offer protection in his home” &amp; “only 50 people were there “ #covid19 #socialdistancingfail #coronavirususa	UNINFORMATIVE	NORP GPE GPE CARDINAL MONEY	catholic/NORP ft_lauderdale/GPE gatherings!we/GPE only_50/CARDINAL #covid19_#socialdistancingfail_#/MONEY
1242860829969715200	dr. morrison. still 3 positive covid-19 tests in pei. close to 500 tests have been conducted. waiting on results of 250. #pei	INFORMATIVE	PERSON CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL PERSON	morrison/PERSON 3/CARDINAL pei/GPE close_to_500/CARDINAL 250/CARDINAL #pei/PERSON
1242791355644030976	rwanda traced back 3 of their #covid19 cases from kenya now uganda confirms one of their case has links to kenya... #ukweliusemwe	INFORMATIVE	GPE CARDINAL GPE GPE CARDINAL GPE	rwanda/GPE 3/CARDINAL kenya/GPE uganda/GPE one/CARDINAL kenya/GPE
1241492383356915715	#breaking | florida adds 200 new cases of covid-19 today, and 2 new deaths. roughly 50% of the cases in the state come from palm beach, broward and miami-dade counties. @user #coronavirus httpurl	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL DATE CARDINAL PERCENT GPE GPE GPE CARDINAL	#/CARDINAL florida/GPE 200/CARDINAL today/DATE 2/CARDINAL roughly_50%/PERCENT palm_beach/GPE broward/GPE miami-dade/GPE #/CARDINAL
1241677885808795651	and btw, there was a confirm case of covid19 in aziz bhatti &amp; his son also tested positive. we have so many spain &amp; italy return people swarming the hospitals without masks &amp; coming in opds for minor illnesses. this is the state of the affairs here. the end.	INFORMATIVE	ORG ORG GPE	aziz_bhatti_&amp/ORG spain_&amp/ORG italy/GPE
1236143874004877314	pence and mcconnell attended the aipac conference where two attendees have tested positive for the coronavirus. #wtp2020 #wtpteam #wtpebrc httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG ORG CARDINAL	mcconnell/ORG aipac/ORG two/CARDINAL
1241036936560676867	capitol building 202.228.8800 house office buildings 202.225.4141 senate office buildings 202.224.3141 demand that our nov2020 elections &amp; all the primaries left must be from now on a mail-in only elecx process. #covid19 #burisma=.@user	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG ORG CARDINAL ORG CARDINAL ORG MONEY	capitol_building/ORG 202.228.8800_house/ORG 202.225.4141/CARDINAL senate/ORG 202.224.3141/CARDINAL nov2020_elections_&amp/ORG #covid19_#/MONEY
1249502697352581120	the story of covid-19's effects on western new york has largely been one of mind-numbing data, provided day after day on a national, state, county and even municipal level. but sunday's death notices in the buffalo news told a very different story. httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE GPE CARDINAL DATE ORG	covid-19/GPE new_york/GPE one/CARDINAL sunday/DATE the_buffalo_news/ORG
1238285142302441472	"it couldn't have happened to a nicer person? then again, this ""virus"" is a joke. a bad one at that. hope it's not that one in a million fatal cases. 👇🏼👇🏼👇🏼 canadian pm justin trudeau's wife, sophie, tests positive for coronavirus, officials say httpurl"	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL CARDINAL NORP PERSON PERSON	one/CARDINAL a_million/CARDINAL canadian/NORP justin_trudeau's/PERSON sophie/PERSON
1245951063842148352	dear @user - don’t be an idiot, you might have heard about a #pandemic which is killing thousands of residents in #football loving countries? let organizations and countries decide what to do with their competions based on #science and experts’ advise? -#covid19 httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	CARDINAL CARDINAL	#/CARDINAL thousands/CARDINAL
1245893820534923265	indonesia frees 18,000 inmates, as it records highest #coronavirus death toll in asia behind china httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL LOC GPE	indonesia/GPE 18,000/CARDINAL #/CARDINAL asia/LOC china/GPE
1241123604097454080	breaking: there are 77 new cases of #covid19 in bc, bringing the provincial total to 348. there are no new deaths. dr. bonnie henry says there are front-line workers who are getting infected. has nice words to say about those working around the clock to help others. @user	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL PERSON	77/CARDINAL bc/GPE 348/CARDINAL bonnie_henry/PERSON
1241682205048541185	five things to help stop the spread of coronavirus 1. wash your handsflexed biceps 2. cough/sneeze into your elbow 3. don't touch your face straight ruler 4. stay more than 3ft (1m) away from others house with garden 5. stay home if you feel sick #coronafreepakistan	UNINFORMATIVE	CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL	five/CARDINAL 1/CARDINAL 2/CARDINAL 3/CARDINAL 4/CARDINAL more_than_3/CARDINAL 5/CARDINAL
1244605203434950656	the monday moment: three scoops, three sides of the story httpurl thanks to the @user @user + @user as well as @user and @user for the journos + inspiration in casano's case. --- #coco @user #covid_19	UNINFORMATIVE	DATE CARDINAL CARDINAL ORG ORG ORG	monday/DATE three/CARDINAL three/CARDINAL the_@user_@user_+_@user/ORG @user/ORG @user/ORG
1241041852515614721	the second case of covid-19 in #pei was travelling on air canada flight 756 from toronto to charlottetown. it left toronto at 9:20 am march 11 and arrived in pei at 12:28 @user	INFORMATIVE	ORDINAL GPE GPE ORG CARDINAL GPE GPE GPE TIME GPE	second/ORDINAL covid-19/GPE #pei/GPE air_canada/ORG 756/CARDINAL toronto/GPE charlottetown/GPE toronto/GPE 9:20_am_march_11/TIME pei/GPE
1245854723866910720	@user @user but they have never measured dr with total positive test data before. sars, swine flu, influenza they... cdc... has always used total estimated cases. if we use that same equation for covid19 it's more like .2% or less	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG PERCENT	cdc/ORG like_.2%/PERCENT
1241628385056444418	a 38-year-old man has passed away in bihar today due to kidney failure; he has been tested positive for #covid19. he was from munger. he died yesterday at aiims in patna; had returned from kolkata two days back: dr. prabhat kumar singh, aiims patna, bihar	INFORMATIVE	DATE GPE DATE PERSON DATE ORG GPE GPE DATE PERSON ORG GPE	38-year-old/DATE bihar/GPE today/DATE munger/PERSON yesterday/DATE aiims/ORG patna/GPE kolkata/GPE two_days/DATE prabhat_kumar_singh/PERSON aiims_patna/ORG bihar/GPE
1241193660823359488	freebird httpurl #coronavirus time for freebird #budweiser @user what song is it you want to hear?	UNINFORMATIVE	CARDINAL	#/CARDINAL
1241782730087714818	here's the latest on the #coronavirus: - deaths in spain jumped 30% for a third day - italy death toil reaches 671 - global cases doubled in a week to over 300,000 - german economy to shrink 5%, bild says - a third of china cases showed no symptoms	INFORMATIVE	GPE PERCENT DATE CARDINAL DATE CARDINAL PERCENT PERSON ORDINAL GPE	spain/GPE 30%/PERCENT a_third_day/DATE 671/CARDINAL a_week/DATE over_300,000_-_german/CARDINAL 5%/PERCENT bild/PERSON third/ORDINAL china/GPE
1245829491064287233	@user so sad nigerian medical doctor dies of coronavirus in the united kingdom. please do not compromise your👇 #washyourhands #staysafe #stayhome #socialdistancing #covidー19 httpurl	INFORMATIVE	NORP GPE	nigerian/NORP the_united_kingdom/GPE
1237947244331954176	stephen harper, mike pence attend conference where two test positive for covid-19 httpurl	INFORMATIVE	PERSON PERSON CARDINAL	stephen_harper/PERSON mike_pence/PERSON two/CARDINAL
1247024517941268481	@user now i get it. there was no new news on covid-19.. trump called a 7pm news conference because biden had a video town hall at 7pm. it was political. good news.. trump gave biden lots of material for a truthful but ugly campaign ad! @user @user @user	UNINFORMATIVE	DATE PERSON TIME PERSON TIME PERSON PERSON	covid-19/DATE trump/PERSON 7pm/TIME biden/PERSON 7pm/TIME trump/PERSON biden/PERSON
1245906591486001155	this ends as of college football season regardless of the death toll or the south really will rise again and not for a deplorable cause. #collegefootball #coronavirus	UNINFORMATIVE	LOC PERSON	south/LOC #collegefootball_#/PERSON
1245709193895706626	these covid-19 care cards are a great way to plan your day, keep yourself motivated and build a positive outlook while working or learning from home #stayhomesavelives httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE PERCENT	covid-19/GPE #stayhomesavelives/PERCENT
1238918620413116416	increase in covid-19 cases in 1 day in europe: portugal 51% estonia 46% finland 45% uk 43% czechia 33% austria, ireland 30% slovenia 28% germany, france, belgium 23% spain, switzerland 21% italy, greece 20% netherlands, romania 19% sweden 18% iceland 16% norway 8% denmark 3%	UNINFORMATIVE	DATE DATE LOC GPE PERCENT GPE PERCENT GPE PERCENT PERCENT PERCENT GPE GPE PERCENT GPE PERCENT GPE GPE GPE PERCENT GPE GPE PERCENT GPE GPE PERCENT GPE GPE PERCENT GPE PERCENT GPE PERCENT GPE PERCENT GPE PERCENT	covid-19/DATE 1_day/DATE europe/LOC portugal/GPE 51%/PERCENT estonia/GPE 46%/PERCENT finland/GPE 45%/PERCENT 43%/PERCENT 33%/PERCENT austria/GPE ireland/GPE 30%/PERCENT slovenia/GPE 28%/PERCENT germany/GPE france/GPE belgium/GPE 23%/PERCENT spain/GPE switzerland/GPE 21%/PERCENT italy/GPE greece/GPE 20%/PERCENT netherlands/GPE romania/GPE 19%/PERCENT sweden/GPE 18%/PERCENT iceland/GPE 16%/PERCENT norway/GPE 8%/PERCENT denmark/GPE 3%/PERCENT
1242910874953809923	happening now: mayor @user and @user commissioner les miller, and county administrator mike merrill are live to provide an update on covid-19 following today’s meeting of the hillsborough county emergency policy group. watch: httpurl httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG PERSON PERSON GPE DATE GPE	@user/ORG les_miller/PERSON mike_merrill/PERSON covid-19/GPE today/DATE hillsborough_county/GPE
1241672591980425216	brenda murphy: there haven’t been any published cases of #covid infection through a school. didn’t this pandemic just start &amp; isn’t the entire world learning as we go? who’d have time to physically deal with covid-19 &amp; write a paper about it at the same time? #closeschoolsnow	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON ORG ORG PERSON	brenda_murphy/PERSON &amp/ORG covid-19_&amp/ORG #closeschoolsnow/PERSON
1241064367887613954	correction: pa has 83 new cases of covid-19, bringing our statewide total to 268 cases, said pa health secretary dr. rachel levine. that's more than double the new cases wednesday**.	INFORMATIVE	GPE CARDINAL DATE CARDINAL ORG PERSON DATE	pa/GPE 83/CARDINAL covid-19/DATE 268/CARDINAL pa_health/ORG rachel_levine/PERSON wednesday/DATE
1247341639712083969	fauci said: 1)covid19 nothing to worry about-then he said it was; 2)no need to wear masks-then he said there was; 3)treatment proposed by our president wasn’t effective-yet, it was. fauci-an expert on infectious disease?🙄 no wonder our healthcare system is failing.#firefauci	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL PERSON	fauci/ORG 1)covid19/CARDINAL 2)no/CARDINAL 3)treatment/CARDINAL fauci/PERSON
1247076840621125632	two men with coronavirus have died in balkh province, provincial health officials confirmed on monday, adding that one was an 86-year-old who died in a hospital, and the other was 70 and died at home. so far three people have died of #coronavirus in balkh province. #afghanistan httpurl	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL GPE DATE DATE DATE CARDINAL GPE	two/CARDINAL balkh_province/GPE monday/DATE 86-year-old/DATE 70/DATE three/CARDINAL balkh_province/GPE
1242087505412919302	once again, @user was right! deep state #drfauci was being unnecessarily negative. optimism and hope is the remedy to this crisis. negativity only fuels the left's narrative! dr. oz: my 'jaw dropped' at hopeful coronavirus trial results httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG PERSON PERSON	@user/ORG #drfauci/PERSON oz/PERSON
1236132820042551306	@user @user i wouldn't go near stanford, let alone santa clara county. the border ended with palo alto for me, but once i found out the stanford doctor got infected with the plague, thats a no go zone. at least till the cases stop multiplying. don't feel safer in sf but thats #covid19 life.	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG GPE GPE ORG MONEY	stanford/ORG santa_clara_county/GPE palo_alto/GPE stanford/ORG #covid19/MONEY
1241420552943702016	will the #worldend on april 29, 2020? know the truth! an asteroid approx. 1.8 km to 4.1 km in size, will fly past #earth from a safe distance of 3.9 million miles at an expected speed of around 20000 mph. #29thapril2020 #asteroid #corona #coronavirus httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG DATE QUANTITY QUANTITY QUANTITY QUANTITY	worldend/ORG april_29,_2020/DATE 1.8_km_to/QUANTITY 4.1_km/QUANTITY 3.9_million_miles/QUANTITY around_20000_mph/QUANTITY
1241773598903283719	#iraq on sunday imposed a total nationwide lockdown until march 28 to fight the novel #coronavirus, as the number of cases grew and the death toll climbed to 20.	INFORMATIVE	GPE DATE DATE CARDINAL	iraq/GPE sunday/DATE march_28/DATE 20/CARDINAL
1236079389034663936	**coronavirus in md. update** @user is asking anyone at the village of rockville, a retirement community, feb. 29 between noon-6pm to see their health provider to be tested. to date in md. 44 people tested, 33 negative, 3 positive and 8 tests are pending. @user httpurl	INFORMATIVE	GPE GPE DATE GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL	md/GPE rockville/GPE feb._29/DATE md/GPE 44/CARDINAL 33/CARDINAL 3/CARDINAL 8/CARDINAL
1236147161156521985	another korean air flight attendant confirmed for coronavirus. she was part of the crew for korea to la. diagnosed after returning to korea.	INFORMATIVE	NORP GPE GPE GPE	korean/NORP korea/GPE la/GPE korea/GPE
1236509902333284352	@user the country like japan and us that does not test or does less will lose the war against covid19. south korea, italy, uk carry out large tests. s.korea 178,189 tested, italy 42,062 tested. testing the suspected people is like removing mines from ground.	INFORMATIVE	GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL	japan/GPE us/GPE south_korea/GPE italy/GPE uk/GPE s.korea/GPE 178,189/CARDINAL 42,062/CARDINAL
1241123700197466112	the infographic shows the spread of #covid19 outside of china. #ireland has 683 confirmed cases with three deaths. brave healthcare works, volunteers, communities are giving everything to contain the virus and assist each other in this difficult moment. source: bbc, jhu httpurl	INFORMATIVE	GPE GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL ORG GPE	china/GPE #ireland/GPE 683/CARDINAL three/CARDINAL bbc/ORG jhu/GPE
1241377862164328454	update: #covid19 in africa new cases = nc - 38 nc in s. africa - 24 nc in burkina faso - 10 nc in nigeria - 7 nc togo - 6 nc tunisia - 5 nc dr congo - 5 nc ivory coast - 3 nc ghana - 2 nc cabo verde - 2 nc mauritius - 2 nc zimbabwe - 1 nc in algeria - 1 nc angola - 1 nc liberia	INFORMATIVE	LOC GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE	africa/LOC nc/GPE nc/GPE s._africa_-_24/GPE nc/GPE burkina_faso/GPE nc/GPE nigeria_-_7/GPE nc/GPE nc_ivory/GPE nc_ghana/GPE nc/GPE algeria_-_1/GPE
1246035478857555970	@user instead of make hunger kill man inside house laidis, e no go beta make guy man kuku get coronavirus ontop where him de hustle for street? at least that way man go see chow for hospital, plus possibility of survival too😞😢 the government said to stay indoors, on empty bele?😖😨	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON	kuku/PERSON
1245902586340933645	i’m too fragile for this! 😭 but here is a coronavirus patient success story: a 44-year-old woman who spent 10 days on a ventilator was discharged today after being at st. david's south austin medical center for 16 days with coronavirus.	INFORMATIVE	DATE DATE DATE FAC DATE	44-year-old/DATE 10_days/DATE today/DATE st._david's/FAC 16_days/DATE
1243545889370759178	"$ctso is running its manufacturing plant 24/7. ""cytosorbents shares up 32% after cytosorb used in covid-19 patients"" also on my list $srne, $bcrx."	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON PERSON PERCENT DATE	ctso/PERSON cytosorbents/PERSON 32%/PERCENT covid-19/DATE
1246011700735668228	@user @user just confirming that lowlife scumbags of the #hanson voting type are alive and thriving on #racialabuse in #australia ... #noroomforracists #hansonsonenation #covid19 @user httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE MONEY	australia/GPE #noroomforracists_#hansonsonenation_#covid19/MONEY
1247875653908791298	according to httpurl there were 392,594 positive covid-19 cases in the us as of yesterday. i made this pie chart that shows the relative amount by each state. httpurl	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL GPE DATE	392,594/CARDINAL us/GPE yesterday/DATE
1241171749963735040	#breaking: wolf administration delays enforcement that all non-life-sustaining businesses in pennsylvania must close their physical locations to slow the spread of covid-19. enforcement will now start at 8am on monday, march 23rd. httpurl httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE GPE TIME	pennsylvania/GPE covid-19/GPE 8am_on_monday,_march_23rd/TIME
1241183167199031296	we can get through covid-19. dami na outbreak in the past years and lahat yun nalampasan ng earth.	UNINFORMATIVE	DATE ORG DATE PERSON	covid-19/DATE dami_na/ORG the_past_years/DATE lahat_yun_nalampasan_ng_earth/PERSON
1245845214679445505	@user and he was told on february the 3rd by the military that over 150 thousand people could die from the coronavirus, and on february the 4th he sent our medical supplies we need to china.. httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	DATE CARDINAL DATE GPE	february_the_3rd/DATE over_150_thousand/CARDINAL february_the_4th/DATE china/GPE
1246030193178734593	coronavirus world map: which countries have the most cases and deaths? httpurl httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE		
1236119372092956673	colorado coronavirus cases: eight total patients have been announced, others quarantined. italy, italy, italy ⁦@user httpurl	INFORMATIVE	GPE CARDINAL GPE GPE GPE	colorado/GPE eight/CARDINAL italy/GPE italy/GPE italy/GPE
1246549152248541193	today we @user transported 10 covid 19 positive patients for hse hospitals. my dedicated team stepping up to play our part. preparing for a few difficult weeks ahead. together we are stronger httpurl	INFORMATIVE	DATE ORG CARDINAL CARDINAL ORG DATE	today/DATE @user/ORG 10/CARDINAL 19/CARDINAL hse/ORG a_few_difficult_weeks_ahead/DATE
1249579304221999105	recently health minister of sl pavithra wanniarachchi has said that all the patients who have died of covid-19 would be cremated. it is against the tenets of islam and in contravention of the guidelines on disposal of dead bodies issued by who which allows burial. @user	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG GPE ORG	sl_pavithra_wanniarachchi/ORG covid-19/GPE islam/ORG
1241852053091160065	washington vast intervention driven by terrifying 30%-50% daily increases in coronavirus cases with no end in sight httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE PERCENT DATE	washington/GPE 30%-50%/PERCENT daily/DATE
1241180993945571329	america's grocery store workers are on the front lines of the coronavirus pandemic, helping to keep the nation's 330m residents alive and fed in an uncertain and frightening time. httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE QUANTITY	america/GPE 330m/QUANTITY
1239262457065099264	the year is jst 3 mnths old but we've had enough trouble that should last a decade. 🥺 2020 this was not out agreement oo. rip to d dead, quick recovery to the sick n injured &amp; may god console those who are bereaved. festac satellite town abule ado bethlehem lagos coronavirus	UNINFORMATIVE	DATE DATE DATE ORG ORG GPE	the_year/DATE 3_mnths_old/DATE 2020/DATE the_sick_n_injured_&amp/ORG festac_satellite/ORG bethlehem_lagos/GPE
1246014598207041536	the nationwide lockdown in #india because of the #coronavirus has dealt a body blow to the country’s neediest, many of whom have long backed narendra modi httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE PERSON	india/GPE narendra_modi/PERSON
1245763691812802560	tellimer - kenya: covid-19 proposed tax cuts now permanent, fiscal deficit still a concern: kenya's national treasury has confirmed that the measures proposed to deal with the impact of covid-19would be permanent, which we see as positivefor the economy.… httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON GPE GPE ORG	tellimer_-_kenya/PERSON covid-19/GPE kenya/GPE covid-19would/ORG
1241813747611697152	syria has now reported its first coronavirus case after weeks of rumours about an outbreak in the country. here’s what it could mean for regime areas with @user httpurl	INFORMATIVE	GPE ORDINAL DATE	syria/GPE first/ORDINAL weeks/DATE
1235540066832986112	"fm says that the scottish budget includes increased funding for nhs social care resources. ""there is an intensive focus on getting people discharged appropriately"" and is a ""particular focus"" given the coronavirus outbreak. #fmqs"	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG NORP ORG	fm/ORG scottish/NORP nhs_social_care_resources/ORG
1241567592386457600	@user is confirming four more positive cases of covid-19 in the county, this makes 13 total confirmed cases of covid-19 in santa barbara county at this time. read more: httpurl httpurl	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL DATE CARDINAL LOC GPE	four/CARDINAL covid-19/DATE 13/CARDINAL covid-19/LOC santa_barbara_county/GPE
1236088972679528454	@user russia’s secretive vector lab where they studied viruses, etc. fire, some kind of incident in nov. 2019. month later—admittedly very far away—coronavirus pops up in wuhan. just saying.	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE DATE DATE GPE	russia/GPE nov._2019/DATE month_later/DATE wuhan/GPE
1236132988599128064	hawaii lt. gov. josh green is calling for a 60-day pause in cruise ship travel to the united states after former grand princess passenger tests positive for covid-19 in the island state. via @user	INFORMATIVE	PERSON PERSON DATE GPE DATE	hawaii_lt/PERSON josh_green/PERSON 60-day/DATE the_united_states/GPE covid-19/DATE
1245913939906453504	“ladies and gentlemen, put your hands together for... johnny covid and the underlying comorbidities!”	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON	johnny_covid/PERSON
1245660619962896384	@user the issue isn’t that they begged, the issue is that a country of over 200million people or more had more or less 500 ventilators before now while other countries like ukraine had 3500 which is not enough anymore because of the increasing cases of covid-19. what were we doing?	UNINFORMATIVE	CARDINAL CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL GPE	over_200million/CARDINAL 500/CARDINAL ukraine/GPE 3500/CARDINAL covid-19/GPE
1247596569085476864	pretty certain the thingee for boris johnson at 8.00 tonight is a propaganda exercise produced in the backroom at number 10. this had cummings et al written all over it. #covid19	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON TIME CARDINAL PERSON	boris_johnson/PERSON 8.00_tonight/TIME 10/CARDINAL cummings_et_al/PERSON
1236102540665577474	174 new cases of coronavirus in korea there are now 6,767 total cases in korea there have been 44 deaths related to coronavirus 118 patients have recovered and been discharged from the hospital, with 1 case of re-infection httpurl	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL	174/CARDINAL korea/GPE 6,767/CARDINAL korea/GPE 44/CARDINAL 118/CARDINAL 1/CARDINAL
1245785118939152385	global figure of #coronavirus cases has exceded 1 million and death 51k plus, yet we want social gatherings and congregational prayers. still we can save ourselves and others if we stay at home and observe social/physical distancing. kindly spread the word! httpurl	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL CARDINAL	#/CARDINAL 1_million/CARDINAL
1245799233212555267	this is a nigerian nurse who died on after contracting covid19 in the course of duty while caring for client with covid-19 virus in miami. rip great angel. @user httpurl	INFORMATIVE	NORP GPE GPE	nigerian/NORP covid-19/GPE miami/GPE
1237765564321447936	@user @user @user seasonal flu kills roughly 0.1 percent of people. so covid-19 is between 10 and 20 times more fatal. but it is far less dangerous than sars – the virus that ripped across china in 2003 – which killed 10 percent of patients.	UNINFORMATIVE	PERCENT GPE CARDINAL GPE DATE PERCENT	roughly_0.1_percent/PERCENT covid-19/GPE between_10_and_20/CARDINAL china/GPE 2003/DATE 10_percent/PERCENT
1247816371360104450	@user @user @user no figure that i've seen for icu admissions. but covid-19 hospital admissions all told stood at just over 9000 on mar 30. by yesterday, total deaths had risen by around 4400 - or 245% - in the eight days since. i'd assume at least a fair proportion of those who died were in icus.	INFORMATIVE	FAC DATE DATE PERCENT DATE	covid-19_hospital/FAC mar_30/DATE yesterday/DATE 245%/PERCENT the_eight_days/DATE
1244541568343777287	the deaths of the first british doctors from #covid-19 have intensified pressure on ministers to accelerate the supply of #ppe as after two uk doctors die - a further u.k. medic died after this story was published. httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORDINAL NORP MONEY CARDINAL GPE GPE	first/ORDINAL british/NORP covid-19/MONEY two/CARDINAL uk/GPE u.k./GPE
1237177657571368960	while @user was rallying in #michigan.. and bernie was blaming the establishment.. #teamtrump furthered their plan to distract voters by mishandling the coronavirus outbreak. the night before #supertuesday2, 716 u.s. coronavirus cases were reported. 36 states were infected. httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG GPE PERSON CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL	@user/ORG #michigan/GPE bernie/PERSON 716/CARDINAL u.s./GPE 36/CARDINAL
1246715821696536576	the covid-19 unleashed headwinds which have deeply impacted the airline and hospitality sector, now pose a major risk to the job security of over 2,00,000 workforce employed with the country's private airport operators. #ommcomnews httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE CARDINAL	covid-19/GPE 2,00,000/CARDINAL
1248737788943450112	coronavirus tests that can reveal who has already recovered will become available in 'a week or so,' fauci says. those people could go back to work first. httpurl httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	DATE PERSON ORDINAL	'a_week/DATE fauci/PERSON first/ORDINAL
1248735113447460867	"uch cmd reveals why patients are overcoming covid-19 infection quickly httpurl / @user @user ""for those who are returning to work after testing negative, their action is not in tandem with the ncdc guidelines. after the second test to always stay at home"	UNINFORMATIVE	ORDINAL	second/ORDINAL
1241455968770293767	first, beloved italy, now, beautiful spain. 😢 spain's coronavirus cases leap by 5,000 in 24 hours, now only behind china and italy httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORDINAL GPE GPE PERSON CARDINAL TIME GPE GPE	first/ORDINAL italy/GPE spain/GPE 😢_spain's/PERSON 5,000/CARDINAL 24_hours/TIME china/GPE italy/GPE
1251945735651643392	@user @user 211 * 1.746 usd - that's the price kq asks for flight nairobi - london incl. covid test. which has to be negative to board. makes $ 368.406 minimum. will there be a refund if the test is positive?	UNINFORMATIVE	CARDINAL CARDINAL GPE GPE NORP MONEY	211/CARDINAL 1.746/CARDINAL nairobi/GPE london/GPE covid/NORP 368.406/MONEY
1242445320619020288	so it seems that i may have been right in suspecting that including such a measure in the draft version of legislation that would be circulated for input was a #trialballoon... and it seem that it did not fly. #cdnpoli #covid19	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON	#cdnpoli_#covid19/PERSON
1241032704755466240	@user trump's lying his ass off. he's not stemming the spread of the virus by shutting borders. he ignored the spread once we had cases in the us because he didn't test. today in ny alone: 7,152 cases of covid19; 2,950 new positive cases. 4,408 cases in nyc. 18% hospitalized	INFORMATIVE	PERSON GPE DATE GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL GPE PERCENT	trump/PERSON us/GPE today/DATE ny/GPE 7,152/CARDINAL 2,950/CARDINAL 4,408/CARDINAL nyc/GPE 18%/PERCENT
1241096885982695428	125 cases of #covid19 are now being investigated in south carolina. greenville county was notified of 5 additional cases today, which brings the county total to 12.	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL GPE GPE CARDINAL DATE CARDINAL	125/CARDINAL south_carolina/GPE greenville_county/GPE 5/CARDINAL today/DATE 12/CARDINAL
1236140623473848322	"omg this is really bad #china hid data for &gt; a week! they sent samples from #coronavirus victims 12/24/19, a wk before they alerted #who of 40 cases of ""unusual pneumonia"" 12/31 from #wuhan, a city of 11m the market where infected worked &amp; millions shopped, only shut down 1/1/20"	INFORMATIVE	GPE CARDINAL DATE QUANTITY ORG CARDINAL	china/GPE 40/CARDINAL 12/31/DATE 11m/QUANTITY &amp/ORG millions/CARDINAL
1250035925704478722	@user weekly actual deaths in wales &amp; england. last 5 yrs green, yr to 3rd april black. expected no of deaths without cv would have been 9-12000. total no of covid deaths announced that week was 2851 in all uk. indicates that actual death rates are 50-150% higher than those announced. httpurl	INFORMATIVE	DATE ORG GPE DATE DATE CARDINAL NORP DATE CARDINAL GPE PERCENT	weekly/DATE wales_&amp/ORG england/GPE last_5_yrs/DATE april/DATE 9-12000/CARDINAL covid/NORP that_week/DATE 2851/CARDINAL uk/GPE 50-150%/PERCENT
1250731064965730305	in belagavi there are 3rd highest covid19 cases in k'taka, no testing lab yet in uttar k'taka region, bgv badly in of lab #belagavineedscovid19testinglab @user @user @user @user @user @user httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG ORDINAL GPE GPE ORG MONEY	belagavi/ORG 3rd/ORDINAL k'taka/GPE uttar_k'taka_region/GPE bgv/ORG #belagavineedscovid19testinglab/MONEY
1242950839230054401	australia - taking the neoliberal path and letting workers go bankrupt during covid-19. tell @user that we need: 1) rent and mortgage freeze for 6 months, nationwide. 2) gauranteed basic income.	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE DATE CARDINAL DATE CARDINAL	australia/GPE covid-19/DATE 1/CARDINAL 6_months/DATE 2/CARDINAL
1244468889037074432	#icymi: on friday we revealed that nsw domestic violence frontline workers are already seeing devastating effects of #coronavirus on their clients' lives. a survey from @user found 4/10 of those surveyed had reported an increase in client numbers. #thedrum httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	DATE ORG CARDINAL	friday/DATE @user/ORG 4/10/CARDINAL
1247117045629693952	lagos state commissioner of health has confirmed that a 36 year old man has died of coronavirus in lagos state. his death was announced by professor akin abayomi, on twitter today april 5. httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG DATE GPE ORG DATE	lagos_state_commissioner/ORG 36_year_old/DATE lagos/GPE twitter/ORG today_april_5/DATE
1247421368964132864	tuscumbia — it's normally only flown during certain holidays, but the giant u.s. flag has been hung from the north main street side of the colbert county courthouse to lift the spirits of residents coping with the fallout from the coronavirus pandem… httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG GPE GPE	tuscumbia/ORG u.s./GPE the_colbert_county_courthouse/GPE
1246751483502055425	httpurl two more new #coronavirus positive cases were reported from this city sunday. among them is a 70-year-old man and a 29-year-old male according to a tweet by the health &amp; family welfare department, government of odisha. #coronavirusupdates #covid19	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL DATE DATE DATE ORG ORG GPE MONEY	two/CARDINAL sunday/DATE 70-year-old/DATE 29-year-old/DATE the_health_&amp/ORG family_welfare_department/ORG odisha/GPE #coronavirusupdates_#covid19/MONEY
1245937080557068289	st. louis (mo) kmov: beloved eureka high school guidance counselor dies from covid-19	INFORMATIVE	GPE GPE PERSON ORG	st._louis/GPE mo/GPE kmov/PERSON eureka_high_school/ORG
1236104151416721408	oklahoma's first confirmed case of coronavirus is in tulsa county httpurl #smartnews	INFORMATIVE	GPE ORDINAL GPE	oklahoma/GPE first/ORDINAL tulsa_county/GPE
1245206457336938497	"give dem everything dem want. and when "" please standby for an update on covid-19."" start give dem anxiety, line up ""the ministry of health and wellness of jamaica will now provide an update on covid-19"" then when dem cyah manage dat jus tweet the numbers ""update: 5o positive."""	INFORMATIVE	ORG ORG DATE ORG ORG ORG CARDINAL	dem/ORG dem/ORG covid-19/DATE dem/ORG the_ministry_of_health_and_wellness_of_jamaica/ORG dem_cyah/ORG 5o/CARDINAL
1244948352577478656	various sports bodies from the state have come together in the fight against the virus with their arch-rivals mohun bagan contributing rs 30 lakh. #bengalfightscorona httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON QUANTITY	mohun_bagan/PERSON 30_lakh/QUANTITY
1246934929029685251	the latest on coronavirus in florida: 12,350 confirmed cases, and a new total of 221 deaths reported statewide. central florida now has about 1,700 cases, including a tenth tsa worker from orlando international airport, but no new deaths as of sunday evening. httpurl	INFORMATIVE	GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL LOC CARDINAL CARDINAL ORG FAC DATE TIME	florida/GPE 12,350/CARDINAL 221/CARDINAL central_florida/LOC about_1,700/CARDINAL tenth/CARDINAL tsa/ORG orlando_international_airport/FAC sunday/DATE evening/TIME
1236120017025912832	fighting stigma : bhutan bars tourists after first coronavirus case, india total hits 31: “the government will impose two weeks' restriction on all incoming tourists with immediate effect,” bhutan's health ministry said in a statement. httpurl	INFORMATIVE	GPE ORDINAL GPE CARDINAL DATE GPE ORG	bhutan/GPE first/ORDINAL india/GPE 31/CARDINAL two_weeks'/DATE bhutan/GPE health_ministry/ORG
1245430965574356993	there are 193,000 people walking this planet who have recovered from covid-19. immune, they are like demi gods who stride confidently as the rest of us cower.	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL GPE PERSON	193,000/CARDINAL covid-19/GPE demi/PERSON
1236090108476088322	@user incompetence plus corruption equals gop trump administration &amp; gop congress. how many will have to suffer and die before america expels them all from public office? #coronavirus	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG ORG GPE	gop_trump_administration_&amp/ORG gop_congress/ORG america/GPE
1236142335848640512	1.9m icu admissions for usa alone? there are only 45k icu beds in entire country, &amp; each of these patients will occupy an icu bed for 2-3 weeks. other patients will also need icu, so many non #coronavirus patients will die, too. #covid19	UNINFORMATIVE	CARDINAL GPE ORG DATE CARDINAL	1.9/CARDINAL usa/GPE &amp/ORG 2-3_weeks/DATE #/CARDINAL
1241175671646404609	man not to be a downer, but this morning they were saying 13,000 cases of covid-19 in the us and now they're saying 19,000 cases. so either it is spreading fast or the data is just in flux depending on who is collecting it. i'm hoping the latter, fearing the former.	INFORMATIVE	TIME CARDINAL DATE GPE CARDINAL	this_morning/TIME 13,000/CARDINAL covid-19/DATE us/GPE 19,000/CARDINAL
1247382897784287233	usa &amp; south korea had their first #coronavirus cases on the same day, january 21. vastly different strategies taken by both governments. today, korea has 10,284 cases in total, despite its high population density. usa has 10,915 deaths, &amp; 366,848 cases. #covid19 #covid19australia	INFORMATIVE	ORG GPE ORDINAL DATE DATE DATE GPE CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL MONEY	usa_&amp/ORG south_korea/GPE first/ORDINAL the_same_day/DATE january_21/DATE today/DATE korea/GPE 10,284/CARDINAL usa/GPE 10,915/CARDINAL 366,848/CARDINAL #covid19_#/MONEY
1241159758683484166	breaking: the fairfax county health department has confirmed that a man at the crossroads baptist church in bailey's crossroads has tested positive for covid-19.	INFORMATIVE	ORG ORG GPE DATE	the_fairfax_county_health_department/ORG the_crossroads_baptist_church/ORG bailey/GPE covid-19/DATE
1236109824561156096	#update @user maryland @user details new information after 3 coronavirus cases were confirmed in maryland by officials. httpurl httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG CARDINAL GPE	maryland_@user/ORG 3/CARDINAL maryland/GPE
1241551271653445632	latest update #coronavirus #covid19 @user deaths, infections * more than 274,800 people have been infected across the world and 11,389 have died, according to a reuters tally @user	INFORMATIVE	MONEY CARDINAL CARDINAL ORG	#coronavirus_#covid19/MONEY more_than_274,800/CARDINAL 11,389/CARDINAL reuters/ORG
1236113819207782400	being handed out at tollbooths in south korea. well done south korea! #kapshikatshida #southkorea #killthevirus #coronavirus #covid19 #stayhealthy httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE GPE PERSON MONEY MONEY	south_korea/GPE south_korea/GPE #kapshikatshida/PERSON #killthevirus_#/MONEY #covid19_#/MONEY
1246673588880433154	#us embassy in #myanmar #yangon urging its citizens to take the opportunity to leave country while specially-arranged #repatriation flight on april 6 to #sanfrancisco still has available seats. #coronavirus #covid_19 country has 21 cases &amp; 1 death so far. httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG MONEY GPE CARDINAL DATE GPE MONEY CARDINAL CARDINAL	#us_embassy/ORG #myanmar_#/MONEY yangon/GPE #/CARDINAL april_6/DATE #sanfrancisco/GPE #coronavirus_#/MONEY 21/CARDINAL 1/CARDINAL
1241183495302471680	trump could cure coronavirus 19, aids, and cancer in the same day and the media would say he wasn't doing anything.	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG DATE DATE	trump/ORG 19/DATE the_same_day/DATE
1236119243847921665	china on saturday reported 24 new imported cases of #covid19 during the previous day: —17 from iran to gansu, —3 from italy to beijing, —3 from iran to shanghai, —1 from spain to guangdong, bringing the total number of imported infections to 60. httpurl	INFORMATIVE	GPE DATE CARDINAL DATE CARDINAL GPE GPE CARDINAL GPE GPE CARDINAL GPE GPE CARDINAL GPE GPE CARDINAL	china/GPE saturday/DATE 24/CARDINAL the_previous_day/DATE 17/CARDINAL iran/GPE gansu/GPE 3/CARDINAL italy/GPE beijing/GPE 3/CARDINAL iran/GPE shanghai/GPE 1/CARDINAL spain/GPE guangdong/GPE 60/CARDINAL
1241562508005179399	nyc has 8.6m people, 50% more than minnesota’s 5.6m. mn has 137 positive cases, or 1.6% of nyc’s total. mn had its first #covid19 death today; nyc has 60 already. mn has 6 hospitalized. with tests scarce it’s hard to compare any two places, but nyc has it radically worse.	INFORMATIVE	GPE QUANTITY PERCENT GPE QUANTITY GPE CARDINAL PERCENT GPE ORG ORDINAL DATE GPE CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL GPE	nyc/GPE 8.6m/QUANTITY 50%/PERCENT minnesota/GPE 5.6m./QUANTITY mn/GPE 137/CARDINAL 1.6%/PERCENT nyc/GPE mn/ORG first/ORDINAL today/DATE nyc/GPE 60/CARDINAL mn/GPE 6/CARDINAL two/CARDINAL nyc/GPE
1241691345405841408	the islamic republic's lies about covid19% 1_lack of due process sanctions! 2_number of dead and infected! 3_linking the virus to the us biological attack! #khameneivirus	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE PERCENT TIME CARDINAL CARDINAL GPE PERSON	the_islamic_republic's/GPE about_covid19%/PERCENT 1_lack/TIME 2_number/CARDINAL 3_linking/CARDINAL us/GPE #khameneivirus/PERSON
1241191106261528576	comparison of mean no2 emissions over #nyc left - prior #covid19 right - now during #covid19 httpurl httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	PRODUCT	no2/PRODUCT
1236089747816230916	cnbc: vp pence says 21 coronavirus cases on california grand princess cruise ship. httpurl trump partying at margo largo. calls it a hoax via @user	INFORMATIVE	ORG ORG CARDINAL ORG FAC	cnbc/ORG vp_pence/ORG 21/CARDINAL california_grand_princess/ORG margo_largo/FAC
1240329236285665282	cough, fever, and difficulty in breathing. he was notified as a suspected patient of covid19 and his nasopharyngeal swab was sent to nih islamabad through dho office mardan. he refused to get quarantined in dhq hospital mardan and preferred staying at home &gt;	INFORMATIVE	ORG ORG ORG ORG	nih_islamabad/ORG dho_office_mardan/ORG dhq_hospital_mardan/ORG home_&gt/ORG
1236079177268330498	6 days! thursday 10am to 2pm et during (now canceled😢) #himss20! coronavirus, health it, social media &amp; vr-based conferences in #socialvr! during #himss20! 3rd str8 year! httpurl #himsssustainability 🌱 #virtualhimss20 #oculusquest #covid19 #coronavirus httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	DATE DATE ORG ORG DATE MONEY	6_days/DATE thursday_10am_to_2pm_et/DATE 😢/ORG social_media_&amp/ORG 3rd_str8_year/DATE #virtualhimss20_#/MONEY
1241568044348059648	cases of covid-19 as of march 21, 2020, 6:00 pm edt in canada number of confirmed cases 1231 number of probable cases 63 number of deaths 13	INFORMATIVE	DATE DATE TIME GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL	covid-19/DATE march_21,_2020/DATE 6:00_pm_edt/TIME canada/GPE 1231/CARDINAL 63/CARDINAL 13/CARDINAL
1236145818593263617	some rw nuts including hannity and tom cotton are acutully putting out a conspiracy theory that china intentionally put out the coronavirus! coronvirus has been studied since at least the 1970’s. it’s virtually shut down cities in china. and they are blaming obama somehow 🤡🤷‍♀️	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON PERSON GPE PERSON DATE GPE PERSON GPE PERSON	hannity/PERSON tom_cotton/PERSON china/GPE coronvirus/PERSON at_least_the_1970’s/DATE china/GPE obama/PERSON 🤡/GPE ♀/PERSON
1241673946510036993	lakhani hospital in north nazimabad near zia-uddin hospital is testing #covid_19 free of cost. anyone can confirm? #karachi	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG GPE FAC PERSON	lakhani_hospital/ORG north_nazimabad/GPE zia-uddin_hospital/FAC karachi/PERSON
1251729440708587520	🤔 like usps, republicans want 2 privatize it. 🤑 i wonder if the mar-a-lago shadow va leaders, think veterans, &amp; health care workers' deaths are the price 2 pay 2 speed up privatization. 👇 trump’s war on va workers is exposing them to the coronavirus httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG ORG NORP CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL LOC	🤔/ORG usps/ORG republicans/NORP 2/CARDINAL 2/CARDINAL 2/CARDINAL 👇_trump/LOC
1236134706350936071	trump and kudlow said the covid is contained. cases now also in mn ok ct ky ne that is contained?? on the 4th there were 153 cases. tonight there are 330 cases. that is contained? @user @user @user @user #maga httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG PERSON ORG GPE ORDINAL CARDINAL TIME CARDINAL	trump/ORG kudlow/PERSON covid/ORG mn/GPE 4th/ORDINAL 153/CARDINAL tonight/TIME 330/CARDINAL
1236090982850052097	@user white wine to celebrate my 72 birthday today.could be my last with my death sentence exploding (coronavirus)&amp;trump in charge.goes to see the damage done by the tornados&amp;than the cdc with his red hat on.things go on in america trump that don’t want you center of attention	UNINFORMATIVE	CARDINAL ORG ORG GPE	72/CARDINAL tornados&amp;than/ORG cdc/ORG america/GPE
1246022432416247809	today at midday on national prison radio, our audience will hear an interview with @user chief executive of @user who will be explaining to people approaching the end of their sentences how they're still operating during the #covid19 outbreak. httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	DATE TIME ORG ORG	today/DATE midday/TIME @user/ORG @user/ORG
1245900761810288645	the deaths from #covidー19 continue to rise here in trinidad and tobago. we are trending at a rate of 6.1 percent. this one broke me . it really did. as this goes up i feel the pain. hearing my fellow countryman die day after day is not right. it isn't. this isn't the 2020 ...	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE GPE PERCENT DATE DATE	trinidad/GPE tobago/GPE 6.1_percent/PERCENT day/DATE 2020/DATE
1248732523980603392	can policymakers engineer a recovery from the coronavirus? read thoughts from our sonal desai: httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON	sonal_desai/PERSON
1241452863936700416	in the last 24 hours there's been almost 800 deaths in italy related to coronavirus - covid-19. let's see how the uk trend compares to italy's. ah httpurl	INFORMATIVE	TIME CARDINAL GPE GPE GPE	the_last_24_hours/TIME almost_800/CARDINAL italy/GPE uk/GPE italy/GPE
1245872701316706304	@user uv or have heard covid19 not good in high temps. one left in the car with windows up, in sunny fl. ??? maybe hot enough to kill any that would land on outside of mask.	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE	fl/GPE
1241609263048359942	"this week in podcast heaven: roman mars singing that one obscure song reply all ""covered"" in a recent super tech support segment to time his hand washing this week in podcast hell: ira glass self quarantining because he shook hands with someone who tested positive for covid-19"	INFORMATIVE	DATE LOC CARDINAL DATE	this_week/DATE roman_mars/LOC one/CARDINAL this_week/DATE
1236092214662402048	apparently someone in scottsdale night clubs tested positive for coronavirus. all you ot club rats better come correct when you approach me!!! wash ur handsssssss!!!	INFORMATIVE	GPE TIME PERSON	scottsdale/GPE night/TIME wash_ur_handsssssss/PERSON
1241552948993363970	gaza authorities confirm first two covid-19 cases of two palestinians who returned from pakistan and were held in quarantine on their return near the egyptian border. experts have warned that an epidemic in gaza would likely be disastrous. httpurl via @user	INFORMATIVE	GPE ORDINAL CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL NORP GPE NORP GPE	gaza/GPE first/ORDINAL two/CARDINAL covid-19/GPE two/CARDINAL palestinians/NORP pakistan/GPE egyptian/NORP gaza/GPE
1246364874604716032	ajk's 1st covid-19 patient, a 45yrs old resident of sudhnoti who had returned from taftan, has fully recovered after his tests on 2 consecutive days tested -ve. he was allowed 2day to go home from mirpur isolation hospital. let's pray remaining 11 patients also recover rapidly.	INFORMATIVE	ORG DATE GPE DATE DATE FAC CARDINAL	ajk/ORG 1st_covid-19/DATE taftan/GPE 2_consecutive_days/DATE 2day/DATE mirpur_isolation_hospital/FAC 11/CARDINAL
1236155890123694080	total confirmed cases of #coronavirus in #southkorea jump to 6,767 &amp; 46 deaths. many south korean condemn government scapegoating religious group and still opening border with #china. httpurl #covid19 #southkorea #covidー19 httpurl	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL MONEY CARDINAL CARDINAL NORP GPE MONEY	#/CARDINAL #southkorea/MONEY 6,767/CARDINAL 46/CARDINAL south_korean/NORP china/GPE #covid19_#/MONEY
1245959717853237254	yesterday, hubei province announced it will honor 14 martyrs of the #covid19 pandemic. among them is #liwenliang, the ophthalmologist police punished for trying to warn his colleagues about the virus that ultimately killed him. httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	DATE GPE CARDINAL PERSON	yesterday/DATE hubei_province/GPE 14/CARDINAL #liwenliang/PERSON
1238896541705932802	spida posts video update 🙏: donovan mitchell says ‘things are going well’ during recovery from the coronavirus 🎥 (@user httpurl #nba	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG PERSON PERSON	spida_posts_video/ORG donovan_mitchell/PERSON 🎥/PERSON
1247237950641000451	@user @user ask him about this story: the first jail inmate to test positive for covid-19 at rikers island, michael tyson, has died. tyson was jailed for parole violation: httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORDINAL DATE GPE PERSON PERSON	first/ORDINAL covid-19/DATE rikers_island/GPE michael_tyson/PERSON tyson/PERSON
1243773988234342400	the oldest #covid19 patient in s korea aged 104 is recovering pretty well after 18 days of treatment. body temp went back to normal and pneumonia in remission. now doctors are waiting for a negative test result. httpurl	INFORMATIVE	GPE DATE	s_korea/GPE 18_days/DATE
1248911574930161665	coronavirus: 19 nhs workers die with coronavirus - but health sec says ppe not to blame &lt; more risk when in a hospital but nhs workers are also infected in the many ways others are - travel to work; shopping, at home, exercising etc #coronavirus #covid19 httpurl	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL ORG ORG MONEY	19/CARDINAL sec/ORG nhs/ORG #coronavirus_#covid19/MONEY
1241784432710676480	"oh, really, @user ""beshear, yarmuth, rand paul attended event with 2 people who tested positive for covid-19"" - httpurl that was 6 days ago. how many senators has he infected while negotiating relief bill? #covid19us"	INFORMATIVE	PERSON GPE ORG CARDINAL DATE	beshear/PERSON yarmuth/GPE rand_paul/ORG 2/CARDINAL 6_days_ago/DATE
1235395965047263237	update on #covid_19. figures include all countries. 56% have recovered. in china 65% recovered so far. my original american source of data at john hopkins csse isn't available now. refer this source... httpurl #coronavirusupdates #coronaviruscanada #cdnpoli httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	PERCENT GPE PERCENT NORP PERSON MONEY	56%/PERCENT china/GPE 65%/PERCENT american/NORP john_hopkins_csse/PERSON #coronavirusupdates_#/MONEY
1236179941303017472	the first american deaths by #coronavirus outside of #washingtonstate have just been reported; 2 people in #florida have died. meanwhile, #punktrump is at a campaign fundraiser at #maralago at this moment. imagine if obama, or any other #potus doing this during a #nationalcrisis	INFORMATIVE	ORDINAL NORP CARDINAL CARDINAL GPE PERSON ORG	first/ORDINAL american/NORP #/CARDINAL 2/CARDINAL florida/GPE obama/PERSON potus/ORG
1246762678196015104	sars cov1 corona virus outbreak lasted 2 year, from 2002 to 2004 in china. sars civ2, (covid 19) corona virus is more intense. it might last even longer, between 2 to 5 years to eradicate.	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON DATE DATE DATE GPE ORG DATE	sars_cov1_corona/PERSON 2_year/DATE 2002/DATE 2004/DATE china/GPE covid_19/ORG between_2_to_5_years/DATE
1244670248885858304	who will trust them now. saquib nisar kkb nai ju kiya hai no one will trust government and give in another fund now. what a shame. 😔 #covid2019	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON PERSON	saquib_nisar_kkb_nai_ju_kiya_hai/PERSON 😔/PERSON
1235570279654363137	king co. advises high-risk residents to stay home as covid-19 death toll reaches 10: kpic httpurl more w/ ecosearch - news: httpurl web: httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG CARDINAL	king_co./ORG 10/CARDINAL
1236101701658128385	hampton, virginia veterans affairs #va restricting building entry points due to #coronavirus concerns httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE ORG PERSON CARDINAL	hampton/GPE virginia_veterans_affairs/ORG #va/PERSON #/CARDINAL
1244662295415918592	our second weekly town hall on #covid19 &amp; #homelessness addresses the challenges of people living outdoors. our panel features hch leaders jim withers, md, of @user &amp; james o’connell, md, of @user register &amp; join us at 12 p.m. ct on april 3. httpurl httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	ORDINAL DATE CARDINAL ORG PERSON GPE ORG PERSON GPE ORG TIME DATE	second/ORDINAL weekly/DATE #/CARDINAL hch/ORG jim_withers/PERSON md/GPE @user_&amp/ORG james_o’connell/PERSON md/GPE @user_register_&amp/ORG 12_p.m._ct/TIME april_3/DATE
1246404234246909953	14 more people have tested positive for the novel corona virus in kashmir, with this the total cases in jammu and kashmir has reached 92. (gns) #kashmir #covid19pandemic #coronavirus	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL LOC GPE LOC CARDINAL MONEY	14/CARDINAL kashmir/LOC jammu/GPE kashmir/LOC 92/CARDINAL #kashmir_#/MONEY
1241568230214262785	there are now at least 1,274 cases of coronavirus confirmed in australia. nsw has 533 cases, victoria has 296, and queensland has 259. #covid_19australia	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL GPE GPE CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL	at_least_1,274/CARDINAL australia/GPE nsw/GPE 533/CARDINAL victoria/GPE 296/CARDINAL queensland/GPE 259/CARDINAL
1246707712479473664	childcare centres are not safe...blacktown rose of sharon centre has 13 people- 7 staff &amp; 6 children were confirmed to have covid-19 on saturday. another 12 people, who are close contacts of the confirmed cases, have also been diagnosed with the virus. close them all #covid19au	INFORMATIVE	GPE ORG CARDINAL CARDINAL DATE DATE CARDINAL	blacktown/GPE sharon_centre/ORG 13/CARDINAL 6/CARDINAL covid-19/DATE saturday/DATE 12/CARDINAL
1241731282444390400	the number of deaths linked to #covidー19 in scotland has risen to 10 - that’s up by 3 from yesterday there are also now 416 known cases, a rise of 43 in the last 24 hours httpurl	INFORMATIVE	GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL DATE CARDINAL CARDINAL TIME	scotland/GPE 10/CARDINAL 3/CARDINAL yesterday/DATE 416/CARDINAL 43/CARDINAL the_last_24_hours/TIME
1236161153912332294	hawaii has its first case of #coronavirus. @user has been devoting more than an hour. hawaii currently has capacity to only test 1600. officials trying to retrace steps of 2 tourists from cruise ship who disembarked in hilo &amp; tested positive for virus. we are now affected too.	INFORMATIVE	GPE ORDINAL TIME GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL ORG	hawaii/GPE first/ORDINAL more_than_an_hour/TIME hawaii/GPE 1600/CARDINAL 2/CARDINAL hilo_&amp/ORG
1244706458102452224	due to the current circumstances resulting from covid-19, we are moving our ecojustice conference, scheduled on october 22-23, 2020, to fall 2021. learn more here - httpurl httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE DATE DATE	covid-19/GPE october_22-23,_2020/DATE 2021/DATE
1236114176067506176	@user so we now have a total of four people who tested positive for covid-19 with history of travel to the philippines, taiwan, japan, australia and usa.	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL DATE GPE GPE GPE GPE GPE	four/CARDINAL covid-19/DATE philippines/GPE taiwan/GPE japan/GPE australia/GPE usa/GPE
1251340811847041026	@user @user my sister is an er physician, she contracted #covid19 at work from a patient though both tests have been negative she hasn’t been able to work since &amp; her hospital employs them as independent contractors so no pay check in 4 weeks, they’ve cut everyone’s hours due to low census	INFORMATIVE	ORG DATE TIME	&amp/ORG 4_weeks/DATE hours/TIME
1242740022207381504	3. pcr tests are available, but testing is only done as necessary. people will be tested only at a doctor’s recommendation. also, patients recovering from coronavirus are retested before they are discharged from the hospital. 4/ httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	CARDINAL	3/CARDINAL
1248036546906857472	boycott smithfield foods! @user plant here in sioux falls has 80 covid-19 cases...25% of all cases in south dakota. and they continue to say they’re protecting their workers, while production continues. $$$ &gt; people!!! httpurl	INFORMATIVE	GPE GPE CARDINAL PERCENT GPE MONEY	smithfield/GPE sioux/GPE 80/CARDINAL 25%/PERCENT south_dakota/GPE $$$_&gt/MONEY
1241200057174589440	over the past 24 hrs, 627 people in #italy died from #covid_19 virus, death toll rise to 4000. here are some of the exclusive scenes from italy as it has been #lockeddown since last 2 weeks. please stay at home everyone &amp; self-isolate. #coronaviruspandemic #coronaviruspakistan httpurl	INFORMATIVE	TIME CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL GPE DATE MONEY	the_past_24_hrs/TIME 627/CARDINAL italy/GPE 4000/CARDINAL italy/GPE last_2_weeks/DATE #coronaviruspandemic_#/MONEY
1245674960158257153	:&gt;deaths and illness from the #coronavirus #pandemic will cause a “very, very painful two weeks,” according to president donald #trump. the #dowjones lost 973.65 points or 4.44%, to close at 20,943.51. the s&amp;p 500 fell 114.09 points or 4.41% futures 65.51 httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	DATE PERSON CARDINAL PERCENT CARDINAL CARDINAL PERCENT	two_weeks/DATE donald_#trump/PERSON 973.65/CARDINAL 4.44%/PERCENT 500/CARDINAL 114.09/CARDINAL 4.41%/PERCENT
1250174623473336328	27-year-old leilani jordan died of covid-19 after working at a grocery store which failed to provide her gloves or hand sanitizer. grocery clerks are essential workers and miust be treated by their employers, the government, and their customers as such. httpurl	INFORMATIVE	DATE PERSON GPE	27-year-old/DATE leilani_jordan/PERSON covid-19/GPE
1235580363872915462	fantasy predictions of a v shaped recovery in china have been dashed. #covid19 #coronavirus @user httpurl in fact china cannot just crank up the ‘factory’ because that will risk a second round effect of infections. httpurl httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE MONEY GPE ORDINAL	china/GPE #covid19_#/MONEY china/GPE second/ORDINAL
1241151638749904896	children and covid. 1391 kids tested from january 28 through february 26, 2020, a total of 171 (12.3%) were confirmed to have sars-cov-2 infection. 3 critical (all had comorbidities), 1 died multiorgan failure. httpurl	INFORMATIVE	NORP CARDINAL DATE CARDINAL PERCENT CARDINAL CARDINAL	covid/NORP 1391/CARDINAL january_28_through_february_26,_2020/DATE 171/CARDINAL 12.3%/PERCENT 3/CARDINAL 1/CARDINAL
1241075255948521472	#coronavirus cases in #karachi now reached 101. this is time to act responsibly to protect our city and country. practice self isolation as much as possible and step out of your house only to purchase essential items including medicines. #coronaviruspakistan	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL GPE CARDINAL	#/CARDINAL #karachi/GPE 101/CARDINAL
1241448863409623040	the faa temporarily halted all flights into philly and nyc after a trainee in a nyc traffic control center tested positive for #covid_19 #covidー19 #coronavirus here’s the flight tracker. httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG GPE GPE GPE MONEY	faa/ORG philly/GPE nyc/GPE nyc/GPE #covid_19_#covidー19_#/MONEY
1236733669236256769	"from italy's aggressive, cautious approach after more than 300 deaths to trump calling it a ""hoax"" and offering gut feeling epidemiological stats...there have been a wide range of strategies to confront coronavirus. we will see what colombia has in store. httpurl"	INFORMATIVE	GPE CARDINAL GPE	italy/GPE more_than_300/CARDINAL colombia/GPE
1247031862469570562	. @user has urged all patients who visited the st augustine's hospital in durban to contact the @user department to be screened for #covid19 after 11 people (patients and staff) were tested positive. #covid19sa @user httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG GPE ORG CARDINAL	the_st_augustine's/ORG durban/GPE @user/ORG 11/CARDINAL
1249024426613649409	ups continues to work. they haven't had any breaks in work history during this crisis. after the death of a 55-year-old manager from #covid_19, they gave employees thin masks to wear on tuesday. social distancing practices are difficult due to their type of work. test them, plz	INFORMATIVE	DATE DATE	55-year-old/DATE tuesday/DATE
1241816187564183555	#coronavirus updates: • saudi coronavirus cases pass 500 • first us senator tested positive for the virus • death toll in italy rises by 651 in a day, bringing total to 5,476 follow the latest: httpurl httpurl	INFORMATIVE	NORP CARDINAL ORDINAL GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL	saudi/NORP 500/CARDINAL first/ORDINAL italy/GPE 651/CARDINAL 5,476/CARDINAL
1248788178900783104	#covid-19 is not only challenging global health systems, but testing our common humanity. gender equality &amp; women’s rights are essential to getting through this pandemic together, to recovering faster, and to building a better future for everyone. #gbaplus httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG	gender_equality_&amp/ORG
1245816543377649664	the world just passed 1 million covid-19 infections. it's been just 3 months since the first new coronavirus case was reported in china. httpurl via @user	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL DATE ORDINAL GPE	1_million/CARDINAL just_3_months/DATE first/ORDINAL china/GPE
1246350419518840834	1,118,921 deaths from covid-19 occurred in just a matter of months. hi emma, but what planet was those deaths on?	UNINFORMATIVE	CARDINAL GPE DATE PERSON	1,118,921/CARDINAL covid-19/GPE months/DATE emma/PERSON
1244436773679312907	the 15th case in us was confirmed thursday. a texans who was evacuated from china was found to have fever &amp; diagnosed as novel coronavirus. the patient is now being treated at methodist hospital in balcons heights. the patient was isolated at all times. httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORDINAL DATE NORP GPE ORG GPE	15th/ORDINAL thursday/DATE texans/NORP china/GPE methodist_hospital/ORG balcons_heights/GPE
1236156627260145670	italy has become the fastest country spreading #coronavirus but trump won’t restrict travel from there but he is scared of getting infected and canceled his cdc schedule. does he understand the exponential rate of infection from just one person walking through one airport?	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE ORG CARDINAL	italy/GPE cdc/ORG one/CARDINAL
1248996455265832960	@user the saddest issue is how few people are recovering after treatment. april 11th @ 11 am: deaths / (deaths + recoveries) = 18,781 / (18,781 + 29,192) = 39% recoveries are 61% of us medical treatments for covid-19. we're terrible at it. not delivering nebulized immunostimulant? httpurl	INFORMATIVE	DATE CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL PERCENT PERCENT DATE	april_11th/DATE 18,781/CARDINAL 18,781/CARDINAL 29,192/CARDINAL 39%/PERCENT 61%/PERCENT covid-19/DATE
1241451778979377152	#covid19 continues its creep in #cny. in cortland county they have confirmed #covid19 cases in a child under 5 and a person in their 50s. 12 additional residents that are asymptomatic are in self quarantine. #coronavirusupdate	INFORMATIVE	ORG GPE DATE DATE CARDINAL	covid19/ORG cortland_county/GPE under_5/DATE 50s/DATE 12/CARDINAL
1244944263613501441	@user @user on saturday, first birmingham doctor died from #coronavirus not alabama, but birmingham, england--sympathies to our english cousins take care, doctors, nurses, and first responders	INFORMATIVE	DATE ORG GPE GPE GPE LANGUAGE ORDINAL	saturday/DATE first_birmingham/ORG alabama/GPE birmingham/GPE england/GPE english/LANGUAGE first/ORDINAL
1241714149228453888	breaking news | 72 new cases of covid-19 coronavirus reported in makkah region in the past 24 hours raising the total cases in makkah to 125. all 72 cases were detected in a single hotel httpurl	INFORMATIVE	DATE DATE GPE TIME GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL	|_72/DATE covid-19/DATE makkah/GPE the_past_24_hours/TIME makkah/GPE 125/CARDINAL 72/CARDINAL
1240440863525867526	#agbarr has instructed us attorneys nationwide to prioritize prosecutions and investigations of #scammers, #fraudsters, and #cybercriminals who are seeking to take advantage of the public panic over the #coronavirusoutbreak. httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	PERSON GPE CARDINAL	#agbarr/PERSON us/GPE #/CARDINAL
1236630339260428289	pro-israel group confirms at least two dc conference attendees from new york tested positive for coronavirus httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG CARDINAL GPE	pro-israel/ORG at_least_two/CARDINAL new_york/GPE
1247102432888250368	the 9th patient in chhattisgarh too has now recovered and is ready to go home. as of now there is only one person in chhattisgarh who has covid19 and he too is looked after by the team of expert doctors, everyone else has been cured! httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORDINAL GPE GPE	9th/ORDINAL chhattisgarh/GPE chhattisgarh/GPE
1248349453913743360	while this is the first #covid19 death in berkeley, it is one of many lives tragically cut short already across our region, our country &amp; the world. we will never know how this person would have contributed to our community in the decades they should have had ahead of them. 2/	INFORMATIVE	ORDINAL GPE ORG DATE CARDINAL	first/ORDINAL berkeley/GPE &amp/ORG the_decades/DATE 2//CARDINAL
1236134705277415424	“2 coronavirus deaths announced in florida by department of health” late friday night release in hopes stormy will be buried!!! #florida #covidー19 #epictrumpfail #trumpskatrina httpurl	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL GPE ORG TIME TIME MONEY	2/CARDINAL florida/GPE department_of_health/ORG late_friday/TIME night/TIME #florida_#covidー19_#epictrumpfail_#/MONEY
1241278574809645056	qld cases of covid-19 soar 380 per cent in a week. more details: httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE GPE MONEY DATE	qld/GPE covid-19/GPE 380_per_cent/MONEY a_week/DATE
1242700440485183489	in louisiana, 44-year-old andraia sanders died in her home of coronavirus. she was a loving mother &amp; a case manager at the volunteers of america north louisiana. httpurl	INFORMATIVE	GPE DATE PERSON ORG FAC GPE	louisiana/GPE 44-year-old/DATE andraia_sanders/PERSON a_loving_mother_&amp/ORG america_north/FAC louisiana/GPE
1245859590236852225	we are not beggars sir,pray the gov release us.a virus that cant kill a rat,not to talk about killing us?450+ died within 48 hours in nyc alone.if the virus is more potent than our malaria,thousnds would be dead now.#covid-419 have been basterdized to enriched the govt officials.	INFORMATIVE	ORG TIME GPE	gov/ORG 48_hours/TIME nyc/GPE
1241519076763226116	how jair bolsonaro's son, eduardo, confirmed his father's positive coronavirus test to fox news, then lied about it httpurl by @user @user	INFORMATIVE	PERSON PERSON ORG	jair_bolsonaro's/PERSON eduardo/PERSON fox_news/ORG
1236108281820545029	#0hshit #scary #coronavirus #coronaviruscanda alberta&amp;#8217;s 2nd presumptive case of coronavirus is in edmonton; calgary closes two atb branches httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORDINAL GPE GPE CARDINAL ORG	2nd/ORDINAL edmonton/GPE calgary/GPE two/CARDINAL atb/ORG
1241586915461087235	germany🇩🇪 - 22 213 cases - 84 dead - 0.4% death rate germany test centers have numerous patients waiting for testing #covid19 although they did not receive a referral notice from the doctor as basis for the test. in munich, some even tried to bribe doctors to let them queue.	INFORMATIVE	GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL PERCENT GPE GPE	germany/GPE 213/CARDINAL 84/CARDINAL 0.4%/PERCENT germany/GPE munich/GPE
1246210544152936449	four of the new #covid19-related deaths announced today include residents at calgary’s mckenzie towne continuing care centre, according to chief medical officer of health dr. deena hinshaw. eight people have now died at the facility due to the outbreak. #covid19ab	INFORMATIVE	CARDINAL DATE GPE ORG PERSON CARDINAL	four/CARDINAL today/DATE calgary/GPE mckenzie_towne/ORG deena_hinshaw/PERSON eight/CARDINAL
1250873267268845568	"@user ""these difficult times"" - understatement of the year. 18,000 #covid_19 deaths described coldly as difficult. 18,000 includes the non-hospital deaths that this #tory government wish to wipe from their death filled record. the 18,000 is still increasing and will as it plateaus."	INFORMATIVE	DATE MONEY CARDINAL NORP CARDINAL	the_year/DATE 18,000_#/MONEY 18,000/CARDINAL tory/NORP 18,000/CARDINAL
1241670952456421378	kenya is the happiest country in east and central africa, a new report by the united nations says. ethiopia has confirmed 2 more covid-19 cases, brings total to 11. both are ethiopian nationals one arrived from belgium, the other from dubai.	INFORMATIVE	GPE GPE ORG GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL NORP GPE GPE	kenya/GPE central_africa/GPE the_united_nations/ORG ethiopia/GPE 2/CARDINAL 11/CARDINAL ethiopian/NORP belgium/GPE dubai/GPE
1247070704681566209	"a ""long-serving"" nurse at a liverpool hospital has died after testing positive for #covid_19 staff nurse at aintree university hospital liz glanister died on friday, the trust which runs it said. she added she would be ""sadly missed by all those who knew and worked with her"". httpurl"	INFORMATIVE	ORG ORG PERSON DATE	liverpool_hospital/ORG aintree_university/ORG liz_glanister/PERSON friday/DATE
1245718627711619078	ie: coronavirus cases don't just spread evenly throughout a country, they spread throughout communities, leading to metro-area type clusters. so what does it mean to compare lombardy to the us, even on a per capita basis, when huge parts of the us remain largely unaffected?	UNINFORMATIVE	GPE GPE GPE	lombardy/GPE us/GPE us/GPE
1236919964226875392	great, my county (santa clara) now has the highest number of covid-19 cases in ca at 37. 😬 on one hand, i'm glad they're doing tests. on the other hand, i know they're still not testing enough—which only validates that there are easily hundreds more here.	INFORMATIVE	GPE GPE GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL CARDINAL	my_county/GPE santa_clara/GPE covid-19/GPE 37/CARDINAL one/CARDINAL hundreds/CARDINAL
1239972123864514561	a @user report named texas as the third least-aggressive u.s. state in combating covid-19. the rankings are based on tested cases per capita, state legislation and other data available as of 4 p.m. ct on march 16. httpurl httpurl	UNINFORMATIVE	ORG GPE ORDINAL GPE GPE TIME DATE	@user/ORG texas/GPE third/ORDINAL u.s./GPE covid-19/GPE 4_p.m._ct/TIME march_16/DATE
1235981175186808832	@user @user hmmm, latest confirmed coronavirus case returned from italy 2 weeks ago. that’s 2 weeks of walking around north carolina. have you required that anyone recently returned from italy be checked? oh you couldn’t, there weren’t any test kits, even though you’ve had 2 months to plan	INFORMATIVE	GPE DATE DATE GPE GPE DATE	italy/GPE 2_weeks_ago/DATE 2_weeks/DATE north_carolina/GPE italy/GPE 2_months/DATE
1236125643516964865	colombia confirms first case of #covid19; the 19-year-old patient recently arrived in bogota from italy httpurl httpurl	INFORMATIVE	GPE ORDINAL DATE GPE GPE	colombia/GPE first/ORDINAL 19-year-old/DATE bogota/GPE italy/GPE
1249773425155092480	these women came to 🇺🇸 asking for protection only to be locked at a for-profit prison in jena, louisiana in the midst of an epidemic in which ice has failed to keep folks safe. the 1st #covid19 case at their facility has now been confirmed. #freethemall httpurl	INFORMATIVE	ORG GPE GPE DATE PERSON	🇸/ORG jena/GPE louisiana/GPE 1st/DATE #freethemall/PERSON
1236178615374450688	at cdc, trump insults wash. governor httpurl gov. leads the way in covid-19 for infection (80) and deaths (14).	INFORMATIVE	ORG GPE CARDINAL CARDINAL	cdc/ORG covid-19/GPE 80/CARDINAL 14/CARDINAL
1243640946018918401	@user yeah its finally the weekend !! but i work 6/7 days so ahaha.. i have off only each sunday for the next month because of the covid situation 🥺 but i will be rich 💃	UNINFORMATIVE	DATE DATE DATE DATE PERSON	the_weekend/DATE 6/7_days/DATE sunday/DATE the_next_month/DATE covid/PERSON
1236106701805359105	@user i want to know where they work &amp; where in #denver they were before quarantine! mcdonald's drive thru? local gym? grocery store or walgreens? i want info &amp; i want it yesterday! #coronavirususa 2 new cases of novel coronavirus reported in denver httpurl	INFORMATIVE	GPE PERSON ORG ORG DATE CARDINAL GPE	denver/GPE mcdonald/PERSON walgreens/ORG info_&amp/ORG yesterday/DATE 2/CARDINAL denver/GPE
